<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	
	>
<channel>
	<title>
	Comments on: Book: On Basilisk Station	</title>
	<atom:link href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/05/03/book-on-basilisk-station/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/05/03/book-on-basilisk-station/</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 10:33:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.2.4</generator>
			<item>
				<title>
				By: Martin				</title>
				<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/05/03/book-on-basilisk-station/#comment-190</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Martin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 05 May 2009 10:33:23 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=1214#comment-190</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[From (distant) memory, it is pretty rough stuff at first. It gets much better - occassionally great - peaks around book five or six, then descends rapidly into self-indulgent multi-narrative political stuff that could really do with a read of House of Cards to see how to say something without actually taking 200 pages to do so. They also dwell more and more on the (US) right-wing prejudices of the writer and his readership. Not unattractive, just a little smug, and again fascinated with the idea that monarchies might be better systems than outright democracies. What is it about conservative Americans and the Cult of the Great Leader? I just don&#039;t get it. 

Honor does develop as a character, but if you don&#039;t like the &#039;ugly duckling doesn&#039;t yet realise she&#039;s a swan&#039; thing, it may prove more of a slog than you are willing to bear, as her lack of personal confidence does remain a key element in the early series. 

The books themselves are less Aubrey/Maturin than Nelson re-written, so there&#039;s no double-act. At their best they are rip-roaring reads, and the space battles are extremely well-done. I&#039;d have given it a 3, but only because I had read a later one first. Info-dumps of all sorts do remain an issue; your mileage may vary on this one. Some I read, being a bit of a details freak for the techie stuff, som of it I skim, some I flip past. 

Gap is a very different kettle of fish, I think - like a comparison of LOTR to Sword of Shanarra. Weber is primarily a popcorn writer. Tasty though!]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From (distant) memory, it is pretty rough stuff at first. It gets much better &#8211; occassionally great &#8211; peaks around book five or six, then descends rapidly into self-indulgent multi-narrative political stuff that could really do with a read of House of Cards to see how to say something without actually taking 200 pages to do so. They also dwell more and more on the (US) right-wing prejudices of the writer and his readership. Not unattractive, just a little smug, and again fascinated with the idea that monarchies might be better systems than outright democracies. What is it about conservative Americans and the Cult of the Great Leader? I just don&#8217;t get it. </p>
<p>Honor does develop as a character, but if you don&#8217;t like the &#8216;ugly duckling doesn&#8217;t yet realise she&#8217;s a swan&#8217; thing, it may prove more of a slog than you are willing to bear, as her lack of personal confidence does remain a key element in the early series. </p>
<p>The books themselves are less Aubrey/Maturin than Nelson re-written, so there&#8217;s no double-act. At their best they are rip-roaring reads, and the space battles are extremely well-done. I&#8217;d have given it a 3, but only because I had read a later one first. Info-dumps of all sorts do remain an issue; your mileage may vary on this one. Some I read, being a bit of a details freak for the techie stuff, som of it I skim, some I flip past. </p>
<p>Gap is a very different kettle of fish, I think &#8211; like a comparison of LOTR to Sword of Shanarra. Weber is primarily a popcorn writer. Tasty though!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
			</channel>
</rss>
