<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>TV &#8211; bluefacedpixie</title>
	<atom:link href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/category/reviews/tv/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 06:30:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.2.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Episode 3 &#038; 4</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2010/04/26/episode-3-4/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2010 06:30:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[TV]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2010/04/26/episode-3-4/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Episode 3. Defuse a bomb with love? Blah. Moffat, be ashamed. And Winston was so fine. Episode 4. Not at all bad, roll on Episode 5. Welcome back Angels, one of the better new (now recurring) challenges. But tell me why does everything need to be _*the* most dangerous_ instead of _*one of the* most &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2010/04/26/episode-3-4/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Episode 3 &#038; 4"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Victory_of_the_Daleks">Episode 3</a>.</p>
<p>Defuse a bomb with love?  Blah.  Moffat, be ashamed.  And Winston was so fine.</p>
<p><a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Time_of_Angels">Episode 4</a>.</p>
<p>Not at all bad, roll on Episode 5.  Welcome back Angels, one of the better new (now recurring) challenges.  But tell me why does everything need to be _*the* most dangerous_ instead of _*one of the* most dangerous_.  It&#8217;s Doctor Who, we know the stakes are high.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Episode 1</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2010/04/16/episode-1/</link>
				<pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2010 06:43:38 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Being Scottish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TV]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2010/04/16/episode-1/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Doctor Who, Eleventh Doctor, Episode 1. If I buy into the thematic corny vibe of the rebooted series since 2005&#8230;. this is not bad. New producer, main writer etc. It&#8217;s 1130, I should go to bed. But.. let&#8217;s try episode 2. Oh, a couple of small points &#8211; apparently the new Doctor is reportably fanciable &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2010/04/16/episode-1/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Episode 1"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.bbc.co.uk/doctorwho/dw">Doctor Who</a>, Eleventh Doctor, Episode 1.</p>
<p>If I buy into the thematic corny vibe of the rebooted series since 2005&#8230;. this is not bad.  New producer, main writer etc.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s 1130, I should go to bed.  But.. let&#8217;s try episode 2.</p>
<p>Oh, a couple of small points &#8211; apparently the new Doctor is reportably fanciable and the new companion is a &#8220;Scottish&#8221; redhead hottie.  And the techtoy (the <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/TARDIS">TARDIS</a>) is all crappy retro-cyber-steampunk. </p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>I don&#8217;t watch Lost</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/04/27/i-dont-watch-lost/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2009 03:12:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog This]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TV]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2009/04/27/i-dont-watch-lost/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[But a penny for my re-posting of thoughts comparing it to Victorian novels: Of course the reason so many nineteenth century novels are so long and convoluted is because the novels were serialized and the writers paid by the word. They were rewarded for stretching out their stories for as long as possible. I guess &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/04/27/i-dont-watch-lost/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "I don&#8217;t watch Lost"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>But a penny for my re-posting of thoughts comparing it to Victorian novels:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Of course the reason so many nineteenth century novels are so long and convoluted is because the novels were serialized and the writers paid by the word. They were rewarded for stretching out their stories for as long as possible. I guess that&#8217;s pretty much the same as a network having a hit show on their hands and stretching out the ad dollars for as many seasons as possible through whatever plot manipulations they can conjure up.</p>
<p>In defense of the Victorians though, I might point out that in Little Dorrit the United Kingdom doesn&#8217;t just disappear! Of course I&#8217;m not totally caught up, so maybe that happened last night.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>(via <a href="http://www.kottke.org/09/04/lost-vs-victorian-literature">kottke</a>)</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thank Goodness for The Doctor</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/04/23/thank-goodness-for-the-doctor/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 05:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Rants]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Things Mac-like]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TV]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=1210</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[I&#8217;m in the basement surrounded by LCDs and flickering lights. There are no real lights on. Unfortunately the recent trials and tribulations with the house Internet have driven me to this. Since Sunday our usually-pretty-rock-solid Internet has been playing silly buggers. I think it&#8217;s the Apple TimeCapsule Airport thing, but I&#8217;m not too sure, although &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/04/23/thank-goodness-for-the-doctor/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Thank Goodness for The Doctor"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;m in the basement surrounded by LCDs and flickering lights.  There are no real lights on.</p>
<p>Unfortunately the recent trials and tribulations with the house Internet have driven me to this.</p>
<p>Since Sunday our usually-pretty-rock-solid Internet has been playing silly buggers.  I think it&#8217;s the Apple TimeCapsule Airport thing, but I&#8217;m not too sure, although I&#8217;m pretty convinced.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s at times like this I wonder what <i>normal</i> folks do when technology doesn&#8217;t work.  And then I wish I was a <i>normal</i> person as I have just enough knowledge to be dangerous and maybe I wouldn&#8217;t be so concerned that the only solution seems to be to pull the cable out of the TimeCapsule (Apple didn&#8217;t give it an on/off switch) and plug it back in with that little pretty blue spark for about 12-hours of use before it somehow&#8230; stops working&#8230; and our backups haven&#8217;t run since last Friday&#8230;.  With all lights green and happy of course.</p>
<p>Tonight&#8217;s adventures in the attempted resolution (for I have no idea if, this time tomorrow, I won&#8217;t be using the F-word in REALLY LARGE CAPITALS) have involved downloading a lot of stuff to find out I have it already, using the cable direct from my DSL modem and doing a PPoE connection from my Mac to the outside world so I can google &#8220;TimeCapsule <strike>sucks</strike> randomly fails at simple internet&#8221;, running a full reset and reconfig on the TimeCapsule, being happy it currently works, and just waiting&#8230;.</p>
<p>However, thanks to the wonder of said Internet (when working) I have passed a small part of the evening quite wonderfully with the <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Next_Doctor">Christmas 2008</a> episode of Doctor Who.  This was following (also in a not-connected-to-the-outside-world patch) an equally (if not more so) pleasant experience with the <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Planet_of_the_Dead">Easter 2009</a> episode of Doctor Who.</p>
<p>These 2008 and 2009 specials are the swan song of the current Doctor (David Tennant, pretty damn fine), he&#8217;s retiring/due for <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eleventh_Doctor">regeneration</a>, as is the Producer/Director <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Russell_T_Davies">Russell Davies</a> who brought Doctor Who back to the BBC.  I&#8217;m excited to see the non-Davies Who as <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php?s=doctor+who">I think the current Who-franchise is fun, cheesy and way too rah-rah-London</a> to be sustainable and will age badly but does have complete strokes of genius.</p>
<p>But the current Doctor is sensitive and caring the way the <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fifth_Doctor">Fifth Doctor</a> (aka <b><i>my Doctor</i></b> in the same way folks have <b><i>my</i> James Bond</b>) was (although many folks never gave Peter Davison the credit he deserved for that until later)  and these two episodes were good, even more so as they were isolated nuggets of goodness in a week fraught with frustration.</p>
<p><a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Planet_of_the_Dead">Planet of the Dead</a> (Easter 2009 Special): <b>4/5</b><br />
<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Next_Doctor">The Next Doctor</a> (Christmas 2008 Special): <b>3/5</b></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>TV: Doctor Who Christmas Special 2007 &#8211; Voyage of the Damned</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2007/12/27/tv-doctor-who-christmas-special-2007-voyage-of-the-damned/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 28 Dec 2007 06:44:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[TV]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2007/12/27/tv-doctor-who-christmas-special-2007-voyage-of-the-damned/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[TV: Voyage Of The Damned (Doctor Who Christmas Special 2007) &#8211; wikipedia 2/5 &#8211; once you give up your fond childhood memories of Doctor Who being scary and serious time-travel science-fiction and succumb to the new nuevo-Brit-rah-rah-rah Doctor Who of Russell T. Davies it&#8217;s pretty easy to enjoy the show. This episode has Kylie Minogue &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2007/12/27/tv-doctor-who-christmas-special-2007-voyage-of-the-damned/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "TV: Doctor Who Christmas Special 2007 &#8211; Voyage of the Damned"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>TV: Voyage Of The Damned (Doctor Who Christmas Special 2007) &#8211; <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Voyage_of_the_Damned_%28Doctor_Who%29">wikipedia</a></p>
<p><b>2/5</b> &#8211; once you give up your fond childhood memories of Doctor Who being scary and serious time-travel science-fiction and succumb to the new nuevo-Brit-rah-rah-rah Doctor Who of <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Russell_T_Davies#Doctor_Who">Russell T. Davies</a> it&#8217;s pretty easy to enjoy the show.</p>
<p>This episode has Kylie Minogue (too celebrity for Doctor Who, ever), superbad robot effects and a futuristic Titanic, and the Queen (in passing).   It&#8217;s nonsense of course, but an enjoyable &#8211; once was enough, and I could maybe watch it again &#8211; entertainment nonetheless.  The <a hef="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/the-bfp-rating-system/">bfp rating system</a> is extremely harsh sounding in such circumstances.  But really.  A 2 is all you get.  <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Torchwood">Torchwood</a> is a 1, remember.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Blake&#8217;s 7</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2007/06/25/blakes-7/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2007 15:09:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog This]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TV]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2007/06/25/blakes-7/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[From wanderings in wikipedia, here is great quote from a review of Blake&#8217;s 7 in 1998 (it&#8217;s 20th anniversary): Hanks praised the series&#8217; ethos in comparison with Star Trek, saying that: &#8220;If you wanted to sum up the relative position of Britain and America in this century &#8211; the ebbing away of the pink areas &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2007/06/25/blakes-7/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Blake&#8217;s 7"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>From wanderings in wikipedia, here is great quote from a review of <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Blakes_7">Blake&#8217;s 7</a> in 1998 (it&#8217;s 20th anniversary):</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Hanks praised the series&#8217; ethos in comparison with Star Trek, saying that: &#8220;If you wanted to sum up the relative position of Britain and America in this century &#8211; the ebbing away of the pink areas of the map, the fading of national self-confidence as Uncle Sam proceeded to colonise the globe with fizzy drinks and Hollywood &#8211; you could do it like this: they had Star Trek, we had Blake&#8217;s 7&#8230; No &#8220;boldly going&#8221; here: instead, we got the boot stamping on a human face which George Orwell offered as a vision of humanity&#8217;s future in Nineteen Eighty-Four.&#8221; Hanks concluded that: &#8220;Blake&#8217;s 7 has acquired a credibility and popularity Terry Nation can never have expected&#8230; I think it&#8217;s to do with the sheer crappiness of the series and the crappiness it attributes to the universe: it is science-fiction for the disillusioned and ironic &#8211; and that is what makes it so very British.&#8221;</p>
</blockquote>
<p>This show was soo crappy with special effects it generally made <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Doctor_who">Doctor Who</a> and <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Space_1999">Space 1999</a> look good.  But it was black, and deep for a teenager, and probably did have more than little influence on <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Firefly_%28TV_series%29">Firefly</a> in retrospect.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Airplane movies</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2007/06/22/airplane-movies/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2007 17:33:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Movies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TV]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2007/06/22/airplane-movies/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Roll-call of the &#8220;stay awake&#8221; flight back to the US: Doctor Who &#8220;Utopia&#8221; (5/5) &#8211; utterly rocked, welcome back Master (torrented on laptop). Ghost Rider (1/5) &#8211; godawful. It&#8217;s worrying that Marvel have decided to start making their own movies when so many of them still blow bubbles. Music and Lyrics (3/5) &#8211; Hugh Grant, &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2007/06/22/airplane-movies/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Airplane movies"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Roll-call of the &#8220;stay awake&#8221; flight back to the US:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="http://www.amazon.com/dp/B000JBWWP6?tag=ballardcorner-20">Doctor Who</a> &#8220;<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Utopia_(Doctor_Who)">Utopia</a>&#8221; (5/5) &#8211; utterly rocked, welcome back Master (torrented on laptop).</li>
<li><a href="http://www.amazon.com/dp/B000OVLBF8?tag=ballardcorner-20">Ghost Rider</a> (1/5) &#8211; godawful.  It&#8217;s worrying that Marvel have <a href="http://www.nytimes.com/2007/06/18/business/media/18marvel.html?_r=1&#038;8dpc&#038;oref=slogin">decided to start making their own movies</a> when so many of them still blow bubbles.</li>
<li><a href="http://www.amazon.com/dp/B00005JPE3?tag=ballardcorner-20">Music and Lyrics</a> (3/5) &#8211; Hugh Grant, standard pleasant rom-com, one of the better ones recently.  Enjoyed it, D would have loved it, so watch it on DVD with your S.O.</li>
<li><a href="http://www.amazon.com/dp/B0000E32UZ?tag=ballardcorner-20">Spooks</a> (<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spooks#Series_5">Season 5</a>, eps 3,4) (3/5) &#8211; new season remains solid but still on the lower-plateau established by the show from <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_Spooks_episodes#Series_3">mid-Season 3</a> onwards (also from laptop).</li>
</ul>
<p>Having power for your laptop on the plane certainly removes the limits of the airline&#8217;s movies &#8211; not that the selection isn&#8217;t always good, but some movies don&#8217;t stimulate or seem too long in the confines of a large steel tube.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Late night TV while traveling</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2007/06/20/late-night-tv-while-traveling/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2007 21:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[master]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TV]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2007/06/20/late-night-tv-while-traveling/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[(still in Finland, still biz travel, sometime after midnight [jetlag], something called MTV3, in English, Finnish subtitles) So I don&#8217;t watch TV much, and I dislike William Shatner, but Boston Legal is kinda fun. Not as funny as Season 1 of Ally McBeal (all those years ago when I *did* watch TV) but pretty good. &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2007/06/20/late-night-tv-while-traveling/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Late night TV while traveling"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>(still in Finland, still biz travel, sometime after midnight [jetlag], something called MTV3, in English, Finnish subtitles)</p>
<p>So I don&#8217;t watch TV much, and I dislike William Shatner, but Boston Legal is kinda fun.  Not as funny as Season 1 of Ally McBeal (all those years ago when I *did* watch TV) but pretty good.  American legal drama is always, well, *soo* American.</p>
<p>Probably the exception that proves the rule.  Who made up that phrase anyway?</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>TV: Dr Who (Season 2)</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/08/04/tv-dr-who-season-2/</link>
				<pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2006 05:58:50 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[TV]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=491</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[A couple of nights ago I blockbustered the last three episodes of Season 2. It was a good season finale &#8211; no real cliffhangers, tightly written, and the not-necessarily-permanent end of Rose Tyler. I hope that this will allow the latest Doctor to roam free, no longer overshadowed by the Londoner Billie Piper and the &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/08/04/tv-dr-who-season-2/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "TV: Dr Who (Season 2)"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A couple of nights ago I blockbustered the last three episodes of Season 2.</p>
<p>It was a good season finale &#8211; no real cliffhangers, tightly written, and the not-necessarily-permanent end of Rose Tyler.  I hope that this will allow the latest Doctor to roam free, no longer overshadowed by the Londoner Billie Piper and the crass over-Britishness of the new visioning (sp?).  I hope so, because otherwise Season 2 of the relaunched Doctor Who will be the last for me.  &#8216;Who&#8217; was never a definitive quality series (although it was defining), but it was eccentric, meaningful, and it never (in its previous lives) ever attempted to be _contemporary_.  Although maybe the 3rd Doctor was and I came so late it seemed quaint in the reruns.  However the sheer ra-ra Englishness and Union Jack flag-waving of the new version is too much. Too Bush, too New Labour.  If you want contemporary reality, go watch Spooks or the Six O&#8217;Clock News.  If you want science fiction, then sadly Dr. Who isn&#8217;t the place to be.  Currently.</p>
<p>There is hope however.   Eccleston was cleverly cast to relaunch the franchise but was never going to be a classic Doctor.  Tennant, however, has potential.  So let&#8217;s give him interesting _supporting_ companions, some offworld non-Earth stories, and maybe a longer but not dominating ark to use the new longer episode time (and I don&#8217;t mean a cheap Bad Wolf/Torchwood branding).   As the Dr. Who geek at work says &#8211; &#8220;Torchwood should allow for enough UK focus&#8221;.</p>
<p>Until then I bless Season 2 with *3/5*, despite the joyous return of the Cybermen (consider that *+1*) as the crap British stories and poorly explained Dalek nonsense was hard to bear (*-1*).  I don&#8217;t even mind he&#8217;s now the last Time Lord, although sometime I would like that explained to me, even though it&#8217;s buried in franchise off-season novels somewhere.</p>
<p>Doctor Who &#8211; Season 1 <a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0436992/episodes#season-1">imdb</a>, <a href="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/B000E41MS6/bluefacedpixi-20">amazon</a>, Season 2 <a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0436992/episodes#season-2">imdb</a><br />
Spooks &#8211; <a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0160904/">imdb</a>, <a href="ttp://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/B0000E32UZ/bluefacedpixi-20">amazon</a><br />
Christopher Eccelston &#8211; <a href="http://www.imdb.com/name/nm0001172/">imdb</a><br />
Billie Piper &#8211; <a href="http://www.imdb.com/name/nm0684877/">imdb</a><br />
David Tennant &#8211; <a href="http://www.imdb.com/name/nm0855039/">imdb</a><br />
The last Time Lord/the Time War &#8211; <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Time_War_%28Doctor_Who%29">wikipedia</a><br />
Cybermen &#8211; <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cyberman">wikipedia</a><br />
Daleks &#8211; <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dalek">wikipedia</a><br />
Doctor Who &#8211; <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Doctor_who">wikipedia</a><br />
Torchwood &#8211; <a href="http://torchwoodtv.blogspot.com/">blog</a>, <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Torchwood">wikipedia</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
