<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Hiking &#8211; bluefacedpixie</title>
	<atom:link href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/category/outside/hiking/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 05:01:28 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.2.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Off walking</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2011/03/29/off-walking/</link>
				<comments>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2011/03/29/off-walking/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 05:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Being Daddy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hiking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Photos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2011/03/29/off-walking/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Off walking, originally uploaded by machaggis.]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="imgcenter">
	<a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/5573499790/" title="Linked from flickr"><img width=400 src="http://farm6.static.flickr.com/5263/5573499790_c6b7f703b9.jpg" alt="Off walking" /></a></p>
<p align=center><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/5573499790/" title="Link to photo on flickr">Off walking</a>, originally uploaded by <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/" title="Link to photographer on flickr">machaggis</a>.</p>
</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2011/03/29/off-walking/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mt. Dickerman Hike</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2010/07/20/mt-dickerman-hike/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2010 05:33:51 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Hiking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Photos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2010/07/20/mt-dickerman-hike/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[2005-08-12.DSCN5697.jpg, originally uploaded by machaggis. And here is that hike from 2005 I just mentioned..]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="imgcenter">
	<a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/4814634972/" title="Linked from flickr"><img width=400 src="http://farm5.static.flickr.com/4123/4814634972_506cc507c4.jpg" alt="2005-08-12.DSCN5697.jpg" /></a></p>
<p align=center><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/4814634972/" title="Link to photo on flickr">2005-08-12.DSCN5697.jpg</a>, originally uploaded by <a href="http://www.flickr.com/people/machaggis/" title="Link to photographer on flickr">machaggis</a>.</p>
<p>And <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/sets/72157624424242861/">here is that hike</a> from 2005 <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2010/07/20/its-a-view-i-tell-you-a-view/">I just mentioned</a>..</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>It&#8217;s a view I tell you, a view.</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2010/07/20/its-a-view-i-tell-you-a-view/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 21 Jul 2010 05:06:10 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Hiking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Photos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2010/07/20/its-a-view-i-tell-you-a-view/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[It&#8217;s a view I tell you, a view., originally uploaded by machaggis. Brad is here. Weather is beatiful. So we hiked*. Last time we did this was 2005. This is the Kendall Katwalk. For someone who has been doing no exercise since starting to drive to work in Bellevue almost a year ago&#8230; I was &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2010/07/20/its-a-view-i-tell-you-a-view/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "It&#8217;s a view I tell you, a view."</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="imgcenter">
	<a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/4814590388/" title="Linked from flickr"><img width=400 src="http://farm5.static.flickr.com/4119/4814590388_6dfbdb5b87.jpg" alt="It's a view I tell you, a view." /></a></p>
<p align=center><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/4814590388/" title="Link to photo on flickr">It&#8217;s a view I tell you, a view.</a>, originally uploaded by <a href="http://www.flickr.com/people/machaggis/" title="Link to photographer on flickr">machaggis</a>.</p>
<p>Brad is here.  Weather is beatiful.  <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/sets/72157624424129529/">So we hiked</a><sup>*</sup>.  Last time we did this was 2005.  This is the <a href="http://www.wta.org/go-hiking/hikes/kendall-katwalk">Kendall Katwalk</a>.<br />
For someone who has been doing no exercise since starting to drive to work in Bellevue almost a year ago&#8230; I was happy at the top, but somewhat disappointed we were only half-way there!<br />
<br />(*) Despite the damn traffic on the I-90.  Painting the roads indeed!</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tree</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2007/03/05/tree/</link>
				<comments>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2007/03/05/tree/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 06 Mar 2007 06:53:53 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Hiking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Photos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2007/03/05/tree/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Tree, originally uploaded by machaggis. Nice hike with the girls at Little Si on Sunday. Even took a few photos that weren&#8217;t of Lucy. Had a lot of corrupt images on the camera after week&#8217;s shooting though &#8211; very disheartening. Could be a new memory card; something to do with my recent shift to RAW; &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2007/03/05/tree/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Tree"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="imgcenter">
	<a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/412318739/" title="Linked from flickr"><img width=400 src="http://farm1.static.flickr.com/168/412318739_e1448d232a.jpg" alt="Tree" /></a></p>
<p align=center><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/412318739/" title="Link to photo on flickr">Tree</a>, originally uploaded by <a href="http://www.flickr.com/people/machaggis/" title="Link to photographer on flickr">machaggis</a>.</p>
<p>Nice hike with the girls at Little Si on Sunday.  Even took a few photos that weren&#8217;t of <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/tags/lucy/">Lucy</a>.<br />
Had a lot of corrupt images on the camera after week&#8217;s shooting though &#8211; very disheartening.  Could be a new memory card; something to do with my recent shift to RAW; taking more &#8220;burst&#8221; shots; or, heaven help me, the camera.  I&#8217;m going to change the card first &#8211; easiest thing to do, and it may be the <a href="http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0009HTB0Y/tag=ballardcorner-20">high tech new card</a> I bought for 25 bucks.<br />
This raw red tree trunk caught my eye.  My first tendency had been to tweak it and fix the bright background etc, but instead just dropped the exposure a tad.  I think it would rock in b/w too&#8230;<br />
{D50, as taken}</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2007/03/05/tree/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Great Wee Roads and Other Observations</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/09/14/great-wee-roads-and-other-observations/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2006 05:54:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Hiking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Outside]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2006/09/14/great-wee-roads-and-other-observations/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Danika and I are back in town, after our 2006 summer vacation. Expect this post to be long  Ive limited myself to an hour  so you may just want to bookmark and come back with a cup of coffee when the boss isnt around. Our summer vacation this year was a 2365 mile &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/09/14/great-wee-roads-and-other-observations/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Great Wee Roads and Other Observations"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Danika and I are back in town, after our 2006 summer vacation. Expect this post to be long  Ive limited myself to an hour  so you may just want to <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2006/09/14/great-wee-roads-and-other-observations/">bookmark</a> and come back with a cup of coffee when the boss isnt around.</p>
<table id="flickr_badge_uber_wrapper" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="3" border="0">
<tr>
<td>
<table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="3" border="0" id="flickr_badge_wrapper"><script type="text/javascript" src="http://www.flickr.com/badge_code_v2.gne?count=4&#038;display=random&#038;size=t&#038;layout=h&#038;source=user_tag&#038;user=22499205%40N00&#038;tag=rockies06sample"></script></table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>
<p>Our summer vacation this year was a <a href="http://machaggis.net/planetdanika/index.php/2006/09/13/2365-miles/">2365 mile</a> roadtrip in a big anti-clockwise loop east to the Rockies in Montana, north into Alberta (Canada) and then a final south-west dash back to Seattle.  With the impending arrival of <a href="http://machaggis.net/planetdanika/index.php/category/noodlehead/">Noodlehead</a> this is a vacation that we think that we wont be able to recreate for the <strike>rest of eternity</strike> next few years, and also reminds us of our <a href="http://machaggis.net/world/world.html">big trip</a> when we were young and mildly interested in each other (or something like that). It also satisfies our need to see mountains for the next few months.  Despite the extra life that Danika was carrying we survived both the extensive driving and quite a few great hikes, and some excellent views.</p>
<p>Photos for the affair are available at shutterfly in four reasonable installments:</p>
<p><a href="http://share.shutterfly.com/action/welcome?sid=8QYtGrJu3aNUi">Getting to Glacier</a><br />
<a href="http://share.shutterfly.com/action/welcome?sid=8QYtGrJu3aNVE">Glacier National Park</a><br />
<a href="http://share.shutterfly.com/action/welcome?sid=8QYtGrJu3aNVm">Banff National Park </a><br />
<a href="http://share.shutterfly.com/action/welcome?sid=8QYtGrJu3aNWI">Jasper National Park</a> </p>
<p>(Indexed on <a href="http://machaggis.net/images">machaggis.net/images</a> and a sample on flickr as  <a href="http://www.flickr.com/search/?w=22499205%40N00&#038;q=rockies06sample&#038;m=text">rockies06sample</a>)</p>
<p>As a caveat, I feel this trip had bad photo-fu.  Unlike some more recent vacations where I merely had to the point the camera and click, it was hard work getting satisfactory shots.  There was a lot of scenery and it was all <b>big</b>.  So big that it was difficult to squeeze into the lens.  Or at least I had trouble. And it was hot when we were traveling which led to a lot of heat haze and limited long distance views.   While this could have been compensated with (very) early morning shots I wasnt that committed, which is also represented by not taking a single tripod shot in the whole holiday  despite carrying it on a few hikes, and thats just plain bad planning!</p>
<p>So, iPods loaded and Subaru packed (with camping gear we never used!), we headed off, and rather than detail a blow-by-blow account (which you can garner from some of my activity logs <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2006/09/06/start-lazy-hike-more/">here</a>  and <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2006/09/12/more-vacation-hiking/">here</a>), I thought I would capture the gist of the holiday in a few observations.</p>
<h2>Great Wee Roads</h2>
<p>(A reference from the Iain Banks book <a href="http://www.amazon.co.uk/Raw-Spirit-Search-Perfect-Dram/dp/1844131955">Raw Spirit</a> about the excellent-to-drive scenic secondary roads in Scotland.) </p>
<p>In general the US is sorely lacking in roads that are fun to drive.  Most roads are too long, too straight, too big, too dull.  But thats the nature of the beast  we drove somewhere between 4 and 5 times the length of Britain on this trip, in a few days, and had fun doing it, and its because Americans know how to build roads to get from A to B, and then the Canadians copied them.   But its not always fun driving like an arrow on a Roman road.   The pleasure of a trip like this is that once were off the main stretches (I-90 East from Seattle for example) many state roads have a potential to be more enjoyable  speed tends to be limited by random curves, although its always amusing passing US country drivers (in once instance a car coming the other direction <i>stopped</i> in shock).   Although the Road to the Sun through Glacier is stunning, it is a tourist road, and the US accolades have to go instead to the stretch of road down the east side of Glacier to the East Glacier town (traversed that a few times) and the scenic drive through North Idaho we did early on the second day.</p>
<p>The Icefield Driveway from Lake Louise to Jasper won the prize for most scenic tourist road, and the start of the mad dash home from Jasper (when we headed north-west instead of south-west) was a close second to the East Glacier drive.</p>
<h2>Sign Shops</h2>
<p>Danika and I have seen a lot of roads and a fair bit of countryside, in a lot of countries.  We can often tell as we reach a town a lot about it by the presence of its fast food chains (Dairy Queen?  Taco Time?  McDonalds?), its mall-saturation (Wal-mart? Target? Costco? Factory Stores?  Northgate Mall?) and car dealerships (Ford/Chevrolet/Dodge/John Deere).  However I finally had a revelation as to what one of the most important businesses in any US town is: the Sign Shop  aka Graphic Design.</p>
<p>As inevitable as a saloon and brothel in an 18th Century wild west town these guys just kept cropping up.  And with good reason: without a local presence for making signs most towns would be invisible to the roadtripping eye.  I had never noticed this before, but on the first day, leaving Spokane, I had a revelation and subsequent towns seemed to confirm this.</p>
<p>Now we only have to determine if this is international or US only, and also whether we can franchise it like Starbucks and become zillionaires.</p>
<h2>It&#8217;s a cold, cold splash&#8230;.</h2>
<p>When you jump into into an alpine lake that contains icebergs, but that&#8217;s what I did at Iceberg Lake &#8211; where else can you <b>do</b> such a thing?</p>
<h2>Where is the Wildlife?</h2>
<p>I wont harp on this, as Danika will probably insert a blunt instrument into my cranium, but I was mostly disappointed with the wildlife on this trip with a late uptick allowing me to be satisfied.</p>
<p>A decade ago I went to Yellowstone and literally had to swerve past buffalo/bison, wave at moose, stare at animal tracks.   It set unrealistic expectations.   </p>
<p>On this trip there was very little wildlife until we drove towards Banff.  And on the way we saw sheep of some description.  Then a few days later, at extreme distance, we saw mountain goats.  And when we headed to Jasper it picked up  a fabulous <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2006/09/11/7th-sep-06-bull-elk/">bull elk</a> in the Athabasca River watching a herd and another bull, a bear on the other side of the train tracks, <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2006/09/11/8th-sep-06-big-horn-sheep/">bighorn sheep</a> (with horns) at the road side.  I was overall, satisfied, but it was a close run thing, especially as the number of sightings almost fit on one hand.</p>
<h2>Gee, The US Sure is Cheaper</h2>
<p>Glacier National Park, indeed the US National Park system, wins 100%.</p>
<p>Glacier was something like $25 for seven-days, or we could buy (and have in the past) the $50 per family pass to all National Parks <i>for a year</i>.</p>
<p>Banff/Jasper National Parks were c$20 a night.  As in, get out by 4pm or we charge you again.  A years membership is c$70 <i>a person</i>.  Our plan to buy the CanadaParks pass went right out the window.</p>
<p>And once we were there the reality struck  in Canada they want your money.  Probably because Jasper and Banff are pretty popular ski towns, prices were high.   Our most annoying event was attempting to go hiking by driving up a forest road only to be stopped at the base of a (not-running) ski gondola.  Cars werent allowed further (looked like a fine road to me, just no tarmac) but a shuttle bus would take us  at $23 per person.  So thats $46 to go on a 2 hour hike, with all the inconvenience of a bus timetable.  On any roadtrip/vacation there are challenging moments, and for this one Danika and I were pissed (as in American pissed).  So we used the restrooms and drove away.  The family behind us cashed up almost 100 bucks.  Ouchie.</p>
<h2>An Inconvenient Truth</h2>
<p>It was ironic, in a way; we finally watched this <a href="http://imdb.com/title/tt0497116/">movie</a>  before going on this holiday and it ended up being very immediate.   Indeed it caused a small shroud of unhappiness to follow us around.  Because you see, in Glacier National Park, there really are <i>no more glaciers</i>.  There are a few, but not hundreds.  The snow-covered mountains are dry rock in September.  The Weeping Wall  it does not weep.  And, in this prime opportunity to promote the effects of global warming to hundred of tourists, there was not a word mentioned or a major campaign in sight.  The National Parks documentation talks of cyclical effect and not of global warming.</p>
<p>It should be compulsory to watch An Inconvenient Truth  (<a href="http://www.apple.com/trailers/paramount_classics/aninconvenienttruth/trailer/">trailer</a>) and visit the website (<a href="http://www.climatecrisis.net/ ">http://www.climatecrisis.net/</a>) before you leave the park.</p>
<p>That said, there were still icebergs at Iceberg Lake, and as we headed North to Canada there were a lot of glaciers and snow on the mountains.   But at the Columbia Icefield stop where you look 1.5 miles  from the carpark to the glacier (which you can walk on etc), youre looking from where the glacier reached just a few decades ago.</p>
<h2>Food Sucks on Holiday</h2>
<p>Sometimes it does, sometimes it doesnt.  Although we didnt have a lot of fast food ala chains, we had a lot of burgers, pizza and steak and it was in general average.   Our standout breakfasts were from our B&#038;B in Whitefish (the Good Medicine Lodge) and best dinner was pizza and beer at Trubys  (also in Whitefish).  None of this helped our waistlines much, but none of it was really bad either (Danika may disagree).</p>
<p><a href="http://machaggis.net/world/bestfood.html ">Best</a> beer  of the vacation was on the Two Medicine Trading Post deck, watching the sun go down on the lake on my birthday  Moose Drool from the <a href="http://www.bigskybrew.com/">Big Sky Brewery</a>, Montana. </p>
<h2>In Conclusion&#8230;</h2>
<p>Ive already overrun my hours budget for this post, and havent even started the finicky formatting yet.  </p>
<p>However, to summarise:</p>
<p>The scenery is amazing, 7000 feet never felt so good, Danika and hiking Noodlehead were rockstars, and wed do it again.  Now.</p>
<table id="flickr_badge_uber_wrapper" cellpadding="0" cellspacing="3" border="0">
<tr>
<td>
<table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="3" border="0" id="flickr_badge_wrapper"><script type="text/javascript" src="http://www.flickr.com/badge_code_v2.gne?count=4&#038;display=random&#038;size=t&#038;layout=h&#038;source=user_tag&#038;user=22499205%40N00&#038;tag=rockies06sample"></script></table>
</td>
</tr>
</table>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>6th Sep 06: 7260ft</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/09/06/6th-sep-06-7260ft/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2006 05:12:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[A Photo Per Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hiking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2006/09/06/6th-sep-06-7260ft/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[6th Sep 06: 7260ft, originally uploaded by machaggis. Banff, Lake Louise Hiked up to the Plain of Six Glaciers. Probably going to be the highest hike of the vacation (although we&#8217;ve already driven higher). Ignore the shine in the background, that&#8217;s only an extremely large kickass glacier and the Abbott Pass. {D50, as taken, handheld}]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="imgcenter">
	<a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/236583167/" title="Photo Per Day Linked from flickr"><img width=400 src="http://static.flickr.com/88/236583167_0796acd0d0.jpg" alt="6th Sep 06: 7260ft" /></a></p>
<p align=center><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/236583167/" title="Link to photo on flickr">6th Sep 06: 7260ft</a>, originally uploaded by <a href="http://www.flickr.com/people/machaggis/" title="Link to photographer on flickr">machaggis</a>.</p>
<p>Banff, Lake Louise<br />
Hiked up to the Plain of Six Glaciers.  Probably going to be the highest hike of the vacation (although we&#8217;ve already driven higher).  Ignore the shine in the background, that&#8217;s only an extremely large kickass glacier and the Abbott Pass.<br />
{D50, as taken, handheld}</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>3rd Sep 06: Mountain Colour</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/09/06/3rd-sep-06-mountain-colour/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2006 05:07:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[A Photo Per Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hiking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2006/09/06/3rd-sep-06-mountain-colour/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[3rd Sep 06: Mountain Colour, originally uploaded by machaggis. Glacier National Park Hiking back from Iceberg Lake (at the Many Glacier part of the park) the colours deserver a mention. {D50, as taken, handheld}]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="imgcenter">
	<a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/236583323/" title="Photo Per Day Linked from flickr"><img width=400 src="http://static.flickr.com/82/236583323_aca45ef29d.jpg" alt="3rd Sep 06: Mountain Colour" /></a></p>
<p align=center><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/236583323/" title="Link to photo on flickr">3rd Sep 06: Mountain Colour</a>, originally uploaded by <a href="http://www.flickr.com/people/machaggis/" title="Link to photographer on flickr">machaggis</a>.</p>
<p>Glacier National Park<br />
Hiking back from Iceberg Lake (at the Many Glacier part of the park) the colours deserver a mention.<br />
{D50, as taken, handheld}</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>2nd Sep 06: Sharing Water</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/09/06/2nd-sep-06-sharing-water/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2006 05:05:13 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Danika]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hiking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2006/09/06/2nd-sep-06-sharing-water/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[2nd Sep 06: Sharing Water, originally uploaded by machaggis. Glacier National Park Several pictures from the 2nd &#8211; I think I will post two. We drove &#8220;The Road to the Sun&#8221; today, and did a short hike to Hidden Lake at Logan&#8217;s Pass (right on the Continental Divide). As it was a short walk/hike we &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/09/06/2nd-sep-06-sharing-water/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "2nd Sep 06: Sharing Water"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="imgcenter">
	<a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/236583407/" title="Photo Per Day Linked from flickr"><img height=400 src="http://static.flickr.com/96/236583407_4d1196e1e5.jpg" alt="2nd Sep 06: Sharing Water" /></a></p>
<p align=center><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/236583407/" title="Link to photo on flickr">2nd Sep 06: Sharing Water</a>, originally uploaded by <a href="http://www.flickr.com/people/machaggis/" title="Link to photographer on flickr">machaggis</a>.</p>
<p>Glacier National Park<br />
Several pictures from the 2nd &#8211; I think I will post two.<br />
We drove &#8220;The Road to the Sun&#8221; today, and did a short hike to Hidden Lake at Logan&#8217;s Pass (right on the Continental Divide).  As it was a short walk/hike we went with little kit, but Danika got thirsty on the way down.<br />
{D50, as taken, handheld}</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>1st Sep 06: Burned Remains</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/09/06/1st-sep-06-burned-remains/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2006 05:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[A Photo Per Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hiking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2006/09/06/1st-sep-06-burned-remains/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[1st Sep 06: Burned Remains, originally uploaded by machaggis. Glacier National Park Just after the West Glacier entrance we hiked up to the Apgar Lookout. It was burned out lower down, but higher up, amongst the aspens, the damage was more selective. {D50, as taken, handheld}]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="imgcenter">
	<a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/236583448/" title="Photo Per Day Linked from flickr"><img height=400 src="http://static.flickr.com/82/236583448_0a77c8ed7e.jpg" alt="1st Sep 06: Burned Remains" /></a></p>
<p align=center><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/236583448/" title="Link to photo on flickr">1st Sep 06: Burned Remains</a>, originally uploaded by <a href="http://www.flickr.com/people/machaggis/" title="Link to photographer on flickr">machaggis</a>.</p>
<p>Glacier National Park<br />
Just after the West Glacier entrance we hiked up to the Apgar Lookout.  It was burned out lower down, but higher up, amongst the aspens, the damage was more selective.<br />
{D50, as taken, handheld}</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>31st Aug 06: Village 2.8 mile</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/09/06/31st-aug-06-village-28-mile/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2006 05:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[A Photo Per Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hiking]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2006/09/06/31st-aug-06-village-28-mile/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[31st Aug 06: Village 2.8 mile, originally uploaded by machaggis. Our first hike of the vacation, up Big Mountain (I kid you not) &#8211; at Whitefish, Montana. {D50, as taken, handheld}]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="imgcenter">
	<a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/236583481/" title="Photo Per Day Linked from flickr"><img width=400 src="http://static.flickr.com/89/236583481_0cdf399d0a.jpg" alt="31st Aug 06: Village 2.8 mile" /></a></p>
<p align=center><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/236583481/" title="Link to photo on flickr">31st Aug 06: Village 2.8 mile</a>, originally uploaded by <a href="http://www.flickr.com/people/machaggis/" title="Link to photographer on flickr">machaggis</a>.</p>
<p>Our first hike of the vacation, up Big Mountain (I kid you not) &#8211; at Whitefish, Montana.<br />
{D50, as taken, handheld}</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
