<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>House &#8211; bluefacedpixie</title>
	<atom:link href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/category/house/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 04:55:13 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.2.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>First Coat Is Done</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2011/07/25/first-coat-is-done/</link>
				<comments>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2011/07/25/first-coat-is-done/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2011 04:55:13 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[House]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Photos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2011/07/25/first-coat-is-done/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Painter 2, originally uploaded by machaggis. Only took a year, glad Lucy can paint.]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="imgcenter">
	<a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/5976971484/" title="Linked from flickr"><img width=400 src="http://farm7.static.flickr.com/6149/5976971484_9801c46722.jpg" alt="Painter 2" /></a></p>
<p align=center><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/5976971484/" title="Link to photo on flickr">Painter 2</a>, originally uploaded by <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/" title="Link to photographer on flickr">machaggis</a>.</p>
<p>Only took a year, glad Lucy can paint.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2011/07/25/first-coat-is-done/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>The funny thing about habit</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2010/04/07/the-funny-thing-about-habit/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 04:46:13 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[House]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2010/04/07/the-funny-thing-about-habit/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[I&#8217;ll know I&#8217;m settled in the new house when I stop turning left, and start turning right, for the toilet paper.]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;ll know I&#8217;m settled in the new house when I stop turning left, and start turning right, for the toilet paper.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>U-Haul Boxes are Specially Sized</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2010/04/03/u-haul-boxes-are-specially-sized/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2010 06:10:39 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[House]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2010/04/03/u-haul-boxes-are-specially-sized/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[U-Haul Boxes are Specially Sized, originally uploaded by machaggis. Wise men say&#8230;.. Never move. Never move with small children. Never move at the start of the year. Think about the stress. Think about the work. Think about the furniture. Think about the decorating. Think about the extra bathroom. Think about the Welcome Home BBQs. Mmmm. &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2010/04/03/u-haul-boxes-are-specially-sized/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "U-Haul Boxes are Specially Sized"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="imgcenter">
	<a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/4489042686/" title="Linked from flickr"><img width=200 src="http://farm5.static.flickr.com/4013/4489042686_ac77e8f95a.jpg" alt="U-Haul Boxes are Specially Sized" /></a></p>
<p align=center><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/4489042686/" title="Link to photo on flickr">U-Haul Boxes are Specially Sized</a>, originally uploaded by <a href="http://www.flickr.com/people/machaggis/" title="Link to photographer on flickr">machaggis</a>.</p>
<p>Wise men say&#8230;..<br />
Never move.<br />
Never move with small children.<br />
Never move at the start of the year.<br />
Think about the stress.<br />
Think about the work.<br />
Think about the furniture.<br />
Think about the decorating.<br />
Think about the extra bathroom.<br />
Think about the Welcome Home BBQs.<br />
Mmmm.  From Ballard, to Ballard, <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/sets/72157623765137678/">here&#8217;s what&#8217;s been keeping us busy</a>.</div>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Exploiting Awesome</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2010/04/02/exploiting-awesome/</link>
				<pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2010 06:29:39 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[House]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2010/04/02/exploiting-awesome/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Gotcha! Good title eh? Anyway, the DSL reconnected on Tuesday. We&#8217;re hoping life may resume before summer ends. The internet is pumping, once more, into our veins. I just spent ten minutes browsing flickr. We&#8217;ve moved house. January was discovery; February was busy; March was stressful; April will &#8211; hopefully &#8211; be closure. Blogging, uploading, &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2010/04/02/exploiting-awesome/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Exploiting Awesome"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Gotcha!</p>
<p>Good title eh?</p>
<p>Anyway, the DSL reconnected on Tuesday.  We&#8217;re hoping life may resume before summer ends.  The internet is pumping, once more, into our veins.  I just spent ten minutes browsing <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/">flickr</a>.</p>
<p>We&#8217;ve moved house.  January was discovery; February was busy; March was stressful; April will &#8211; hopefully &#8211; be closure.  Blogging, uploading, non-house-focused-life was limited either by technology, Earthlink/QWEST, location, priority, circumstance and time.</p>
<p>We still live in <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Edith_Macefield">Ballard</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Progress (see also &#8220;definitive physicality&#8221;)</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/06/28/progress/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2009 05:29:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[House]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Movies]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2009/06/28/progress/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[My progress has been stunning. Our progress has been stunning. Even though our need to sell is no longer burning, we are so damn close &#8211; the to-do list is somewhat dented and we could turn it around at any time in a frenzied week. And then we would have to move out or at &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/06/28/progress/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Progress (see also &#8220;definitive physicality&#8221;)"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>My progress has been stunning.  <i>Our</i> progress has been stunning.</p>
<p>Even though our need to sell is no longer burning, we are so damn close &#8211; the to-do list is somewhat dented and we could turn it around at any time in a frenzied week.   And then we would have to move out or at least put our child in a box for the duration or something during the &#8220;keep it perfect&#8221; staging period.</p>
<p>My progress, personally, has continued through a list of things I have no real interest in (*) and don&#8217;t want to get better at: painting, deck staining (**), moving furniture, truck driving, touch-up (6 different colours yesterday), woodworking (***), weeding, bird-shit-from-house-cleaning, pretty-flower-planting, ikea-furniture-assembling&#8230;  However, it still quite amazes me that someone as practically-limited as myself can still manage to produce average results at such a variety of tasks with no training (****).  The internet and help from friends definitely makes all the difference.</p>
<p>Our commitment level and progress has led to an almost slacker pace of achievement this weekend (*****).  Many things were still done, but we went to a fun BBQ yesterday and this evening I totally ducked the basement (******) and rented a brutally bad movie that I watched with D for brownie points (<a href="http://www.amazon.com/My-Blueberry-Nights-Miriam-Collection/dp/B0016MJ6HY/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&#038;s=dvd&#038;qid=1246253135&#038;sr=8-1&#038;tag=ballardcorner-20">My Blueberry Nights</a> &#8211; 1 bfp star and slow&#8230;.), I also rented <a href="http://www.amazon.com/Taken-Single-Disc-Extended-Liam-Neeson/dp/B001TODCII/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&#038;s=dvd&#038;qid=1246253174&#038;sr=1-1&#038;tag=ballardcorner-20">Taken</a> which I&#8217;m sure is much better.    This was also our first time watching a movie with the girl, which went ok.  We&#8217;re both kinda freaked that she knows how to play <a href="http://www.amazon.com/s/ref=nb_ss_d_2_8?url=search-alias%3Ddvd&#038;field-keywords=curious+george+dvd&#038;x=0&#038;y=0&#038;sprefix=curious+&#038;tag=ballardcorner-20">Curious George</a> from Front Row on my Mac though&#8230;</p>
<p>This week we buckle down to do some house hunting before some travel gets in the way &#8211; our potential house is gone, to a higher or more reliable bidder, and the pickings are scarce.  Timetable is on.</p>
<p>&#8212;-</p>
<p>(*) not to say there is no sense of achievement for a Program Manager (aka deals with compromise resolution all the time) in Software (aka lives in a virtual world): moving a pile of dirt and changing the colour of a room has a certain definitive physicality to it.</p>
<p>(**) I almost enjoyed this as I borrowed Keith&#8217;s pressure washer and used it for the first time.  I think I overdid it in a few places, but those things are cool.  I think I need to add one to my inventory of tools I almost never use &#8211; see (****).</p>
<p>(***) this could be something <a href="http://twitter.com/machaggis/status/2375378328">I could grow to like</a>, but it&#8217;s still hacking away with little skill.</p>
<p>(****) although it is nice to use some of those random tools that you buy that makes every trip to <a href="http://www.homedepot.com/">Home Depot</a> $300.</p>
<p>(*****) I really slacked &#8211; 6 weeks ago I bailed on <a href="http://www.rnrseattle.com/">Saturday&#8217;s marathon</a> (the <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2009/06/03/lets-go/">trip to Whistler</a> tipped the balance on my training), in practicality the house meant even the half went bye-bye.</p>
<p>(******) this task is the big remaining elephant, both the shop side (anyone need some random old crappy bikes, and parts?) and the office side (how to make a rat&#8217;s nest of cables look clean withough just stuffing all the hard drives and printers under the stairs etc)</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>My relationship with No. 2 and No. 4</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/06/14/my-relationship-with-no-2-and-no-4/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2009 06:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[House]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=1233</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Nothing to do with Number Six. Apart from a couple of almost welcome interludes with painting the pocket door white with a 2 1/2&#8243; brush (and family issues, today has been quite a _colourful_ day) I have spent most of it with No. 2 and No. 4 craft brushes doing touch-up. In my distant past &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/06/14/my-relationship-with-no-2-and-no-4/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "My relationship with No. 2 and No. 4"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nothing to do with <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Number_Six_(The_Prisoner)">Number Six</a>.</p>
<p>Apart from a couple of almost welcome interludes with painting the pocket door white with a 2 1/2&#8243; brush (and family issues, today has been quite a _colourful_ day) I have spent most of it with No. 2 and No. 4 craft brushes doing touch-up.  In my distant past these would have been used on <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Airfix">Airfix</a> models or role-playing <a href="http://www.mithril.ie/races/index_wizards.html">figures</a>.</p>
<p>The touch-up was a little around the house (white on veneer in the bathroom and kitchen) but was principally the bland green in the living room.  Which took *hours*.</p>
<p>Should anyone ever be looking for a c100 year old Craftsman <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/1334057400/">cottage</a> with original varnished wood interior and plaster-and-lathe walls that have been painted with varying degrees of carefulness and quality at least a dozen or so times, let me tell you &#8211; *it took as long to do touch-up as it did to do one coat of primer and two coats of paint*.</p>
<p>But, if that&#8217;s the type of house you want (and we&#8217;re heading down that path again, no timber-frame knock-up job in the &#8216;burbs for us, even if it does have perfect drywall and shining white trim) then that&#8217;s the work you have to do.  And I did.  Even if it&#8217;s just so it looks decent enough to sell.</p>
<p>The horror is, of course, is that if we don&#8217;t hit our deadlines for buying/selling: I&#8217;ll have to do this all again in 4 months with a colour we can live with.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Return to Amber Alert</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/06/13/return-to-amber-alert/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 05:43:43 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[House]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=1232</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Take a deep breath. Have the evening off. Since 7 o&#8217;clock I&#8217;ve had pizza, bathed and bedded the girl, chatted to D, read my book and now type away at this little missive. Oh, wine open, being drunk. No house work. I wasn&#8217;t expecting this &#8211; due to the immediacy of WA State real estate &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/06/13/return-to-amber-alert/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Return to Amber Alert"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Take a deep breath.  Have the evening off.  </p>
<p>Since 7 o&#8217;clock I&#8217;ve had pizza, bathed and bedded the girl, chatted to D, read my <a href="http://www.amazon.com/Black-Powder-War-Novik/dp/159606207X/tag=ballardcorner-20">book</a> and now type away at this little missive.  Oh, wine open, being drunk.  No house work.</p>
<p>I wasn&#8217;t expecting this &#8211; due to the immediacy of WA State real estate our &#8220;contingent offer&#8221; (followed by counter and counter-counter offer) would have required our little house to be listed for sale next Friday.  For better or worse, that offer failed and now we have a little breathing space.  Although we&#8217;ve been going 100% to &#8220;get ready for the impossible&#8221; for the last couple of days.  Our commiseration (we want that house, but not silly want, that&#8217;s one of the reasons there was a housing crash after all)/celebration (thank goodness, breathe&#8230;) involves TAKING THE NIGHT OFF!</p>
<p>Since <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2009/06/08/today/">Monday</a>, I&#8217;ve:</p>
<ul>
<li>sealed the grouting thing started on Monday</li>
<li>worked some surprising magic involving mud, yellow paint and the water leak in the kitchen</li>
<li>done some fixup involving sanding, bleaching, oiling on the backsplash area of the kitchen sink</li>
<li>scared myself by attempting to start to clean the basement</li>
<li>fixed the ceiling marks in the bathroom</li>
<li>de-rusted the banister</li>
<li>cleaned some paintwork</li>
<li>almost died of a cold/migraine/sleep deprivation</li>
<li>caulked in several places</li>
<li>painted the living room such that cranberry zing is no more and bland grey-green-ness rules</li>
<li>started painting the pocket door that people don&#8217;t know exists</li>
<li>added more to the to-do list than I&#8217;ve taken off</li>
<li>done all that &#8220;go to work and make money&#8221; stuff that normally generally consumes most of the week anyways&#8230;</li>
</ul>
<p>We&#8217;ve  had a staging consultation (UK: house doctor), which has left me with mixed emotions.  In general their goal is to &#8220;let the house speak for itself&#8221; and &#8220;be ready to move in to&#8221;  which basically means &#8220;remove yourself from the house&#8221; and &#8220;be bland&#8221;.  So we&#8217;ve been taking down pictures if they have the fam in them, packing crap in boxes to send to storage, and the consultant chose this awful shade of green to replace our red, red living room walls (*).  I&#8217;ll do it for the sale, but if it doesn&#8217;t sell then you&#8217;re in deep ****.  One of the reasons I&#8217;m so conflicted is that when *I* _look_ at houses, I _like_ to know it&#8217;s been lived in, see how people manage things (ahh, muddy boots _there_, kids crap _there_, if you didn&#8217;t have a 2000&#8243; TV then you could put a comfy chair _there_, etc&#8230;) and I know I can always erase their life if I don&#8217;t like it (**).  So the whole staging thing is counter to how I like to view houses (a little cleaning up never hurt) but then I guess we&#8217;re pretty atypical.</p>
<p>Oh yes, and the staging thing is why we&#8217;re in negative equity with the to-do list, which can naturally make anyone feel a little disgruntled, but having more than 2 weekend days and 4 nights to do it all in will make a world of difference.</p>
<p>And I tried to sum up my feeling on the staging <a href="http://twitter.com/machaggis/status/2157914313">here on twitter</a> (I think tweets should be <a href="http://www.randsinrepose.com/archives/2009/03/02/the_art_of_the_tweet.html">gems</a> approaching profound), repeated here:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Staging a house is removing your soul from your home.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Enough for tonight. Tomorrow starts with <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/3055480388/">Besalu</a>, and then we return to the housework.  Thanks to everyone what has helped/volunteered/Lucy-watched so far.</p>
<p>(*) we had insipid blue and green walls (cross-painted) in the living/dining room when we moved in.  We blew it away with Cranberry Zing, a random red from the paint store.  Colour=character?  Too much for folks apparently. Ironically today&#8217;s green adventure is remarkedly similar to the green we blew away.</p>
<p>(**) despite the fact we dislike decorating/painting/renovating and just want to move in, it&#8217;s easy to make your mark (see (*)) and easy to unpack into different parts of an empty house.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Today</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/06/08/today/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2009 06:10:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[House]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2009/06/08/today/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Before work: grout sealer, sanding speckle/mud After work: child herding After bedtime: Realtor negotiations, crayon removal (WD40 is da&#8217; bomb), resuscitation of 10 year old paint, patchwork painting in kitchen, attempt to spend time geeking out at new Apple things I won&#8217;t buy]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Before work:</strong> grout sealer, sanding speckle/mud<br />
<strong><br />
After work:</strong> child herding<br />
<strong><br />
After bedtime:</strong> Realtor negotiations, crayon removal (WD40 is da&#8217; bomb), resuscitation of 10 year old paint, patchwork painting in kitchen, attempt to spend time geeking out at new Apple things I won&#8217;t buy </p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>&#8220;And so it begins&#8221;</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/06/07/and-so-it-begins/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2009 05:56:10 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[House]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=1229</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[And so it begins &#8211; Ambassador Kosh (Babylon 5) This is one of my favourite lines from my favourite SF TV show &#8211; Babylon 5 &#8211; and often reverberates in my head as momentous events begin. And so today (maybe even yesterday), another new event began in earnest. We may be selling our house. Which &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/06/07/and-so-it-begins/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "&#8220;And so it begins&#8221;"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<blockquote>
<p>And so it begins</p>
<p>&#8211; Ambassador Kosh (Babylon 5)</p>
</blockquote>
<p>This is one of my favourite lines from my favourite SF TV show &#8211; <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Babylon_5">Babylon 5</a> &#8211; and often reverberates in my head as <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2007/01/22/i-may-be-distracted-for-some-time/">momentous events</a> begin.</p>
<p>And so today (maybe even yesterday), another new event began in earnest.  We <i>may</i> be selling our house.  Which involves a to-do list at least 15 essential (and about 100 merely important) things long before we even list.  And we need to <i>maybe</i> have it all done in two weeks or so.</p>
<p>End of our life for a while.</p>
<p><strong>Yesterday</strong> &#8211; <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Morning_glory">morning glory</a>.</p>
<p><strong>Today</strong> &#8211; lawn, hedges, weeds, cabinet repair, wall repair, speckling, to-do list making, 3 glasses of wine and an extremely large bag of <a href="http://www.taquitos.net/chips/Kettle_Baked_Potato_Chips_Sea_Salt_Vinegar">Kettle Salt and Vinegar</a> crisps.</p>
<p>Please welcome the <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/category/house/">House</a> category to bluefacedpixie.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
