<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Gear &#8211; bluefacedpixie</title>
	<atom:link href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/category/reviews/gear/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2007 06:07:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.2.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The best goddamn iPod&#8230; ever?</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2007/07/15/the-best-goddamn-ipod-ever/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 16 Jul 2007 06:07:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Gear]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=892</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[So I&#8217;m coming to the end of a two week stint with an iPhone, and thought I&#8217;d pass a few remarks. First of all, I didn&#8217;t do a crazy line &#8211; my dedication stretched to convincing D to drive me to the Apple store on the 6th at the end of a date night. Although &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2007/07/15/the-best-goddamn-ipod-ever/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "The best goddamn iPod&#8230; ever?"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>So I&#8217;m coming to the end of a two week stint with an iPhone, and thought I&#8217;d pass a few remarks.</p>
<p>First of all, I didn&#8217;t do a <a href="http://www.appleinsider.com/articles/07/06/25/insanity_first_iphone_line_forms_in_manhattan_four_days_early.html">crazy line</a> &#8211; my dedication stretched to convincing D to drive me to the Apple store on the 6th at the end of a date night.  Although the AT&#038;T store on Capitol Hill was sold out, I walked into the University and basically walked straight out again.  The only line was for the demo machines.</p>
<p>Secondly, I ostensibly purchased for work &#8211; it&#8217;s pretty important to compare the funky <a href="http://www.apple.com/iphone/usingiphone/keyboard.html">iPhone keyboard</a> to the capabilities of my baby (<a href="http://tegic.com/products/xt9.asp">XT9</a>, not <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/824808947/">L</a>).</p>
<p>Thirdly, the AT&#038;T service plan seems pretty good (better value than my current T-Mobile deal) although two-years is a like a nutcracker around your privates.  But I&#8217;ll be canceling within the <a href="http://www.tuaw.com/2007/06/27/iphone-returns-and-cancellation-policies/">30-day grace</a> as I can&#8217;t afford the $600 early termination ($200 per line) to move our phones from T-Mobile.</p>
<p>So what do I think?  </p>
<p><strong>The hardware</strong> is unbelievably sweet.  From a device perspective <b>it shows what the device of tomorrow will look like</b>.  This is Star Trek Next Generation control panels (or &#8220;adaptive software user input&#8221;) in action, and it&#8217;s really nice!  The phone is smaller than expected, not heavy, nice to touch and the little touchy, wipey user interaction works well.   No tactile feedback isn&#8217;t much of an issue for me, and I churn though different phones every month so any strangeness lasted less than 5 seconds.</p>
<p><strong>The iPod</strong> is drop dead gorgeous &#8211; the sound is good (although they f**ked up the &#8216;standard&#8217; earphone jack and you&#8217;re forced to use their headphones, so I feel a class action lawsuit happening), the flicking through album covers is pant-wetting gorgeous and the screen size is good enough to watch for a period (I&#8217;m flying in a week and will try it in earnest).</p>
<p><strong>The software/applications</strong> is/are sketchy &#8211; Safari and maps crash regularly, Mail doesn&#8217;t filter junk so it&#8217;s almost useless (and crashes), Calendar doesn&#8217;t have to-do&#8217;s and you can&#8217;t sync notes to your computer.  Indeed the whole &#8220;being tied to iTunes&#8221; both  makes it seamless and annoying as my main iTunes  is a basement music server and my address book is on my personal laptop and my calendar on my work laptop &#8211; ugh!  Indeed I had to use a <a href="http://plaxo.com">Plaxo</a> account to get some co-ordination.  Something I have been resisting for years, and my junk mail has increased tenfold since the sign-up &#8211; co-incy-dink?</p>
<p><strong>The phone </strong>is good.  And the UI is very good.  Perhaps the only phone where speakerphone, call merging and call holding are all easy.  It&#8217;s a little strange the &#8220;phone&#8221; is the only way you can get to your address book, but I&#8217;m sure that&#8217;ll be hacked someday.  One under-reported thing about the iPhone is that it has a custom voicemail that lets you a) see who called (I think, even with the phone off!) and b) dial in only for that message. This is priceless, especially when jumping between meetings or cars during the day.  However it&#8217;s this special magic that seems to tie the phone to AT&#038;T and the long contracts, as it&#8217;s Apple-fu working with AT&#038;T that make this work.</p>
<p><strong>The keyboard</strong> could be better, but makes the device usable.  I could type with it quickly, although it was agonizing to enter passwords and many of the applications do not remember information you type into input fields.  This is <em>extremely annoying</em>, especially as there is no copy/paste (in itself a debatable but defendable choice).  In terms of professional assessment, I think it looks very pretty but I still have a job.</p>
<p><strong>The whole internet thing</strong> is pretty good.  I&#8217;ve pulled it out my pocket and used it in the office rather than my computer.  It&#8217;s a shame the data plan doesn&#8217;t include some wi-fi membership though as wi-fi costs everywhere you want it to be free (airports etc).</p>
<p><strong>It&#8217;s as US-centric as get-out</strong>.  Seriously.  The URL keyboard only has <strong>.com</strong>, international phone numbers appear US-ified beyond recognition, there is no support for phone cards, and the address book doesn&#8217;t display UK addresses/numbers well.  But this can all improve in time.</p>
<p>So my conclusion?  It works as advertised, it works <i>better</i> than expected, it <i>is</i> gorgeous. It wouldn&#8217;t take much for me to buy one.   It&#8217;s the whole cellphone/two year ball and chain and Apple Version 1 combo that&#8217;s the delay.   But the iPod rocks, and that&#8217;s why I may never buy the  iPhone.  There&#8217;s bound to be an iPod like this soon, and there will be no reason for an iPod fan to not buy it.  The price of the new iPod will tell us how fair the iPhone price is, but just now I think that (sticker-shock aside) it&#8217;s not too bad &#8211; the Nokia N&#8217;s run to the high hundreds.  (If you only want a wifi-touchscreen device I recommend you run for the <a href="http://www.mobileplanet.com/p.aspx?i=141019">$139 discontinued</a> Nokia N770&#8217;s.)   But a cheaper iPod would break the iPhone for me, as I don&#8217;t need &#8220;one device&#8221; more than a great iPod and a reliable phone, for a reasonable price on a good contract.  But we&#8217;ll see.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Big Ass Table</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2007/06/22/big-ass-table/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2007 17:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog This]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gear]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geek]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2007/06/22/big-ass-table/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Microsoft Surface mickey take: Your next computer will be a big-ass table]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Microsoft Surface mickey take:</p>
<p><object width="425" height="350"><param name="movie" value="http://www.youtube.com/v/CZrr7AZ9nCY"></param><param name="wmode" value="transparent"></param><embed src="http://www.youtube.com/v/CZrr7AZ9nCY" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" wmode="transparent" width="425" height="350"></embed></object></p>
<blockquote>
<p>Your next computer will be a big-ass table</p>
</blockquote>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Year of Photos</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2007/01/01/a-year-of-photos/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2007 20:20:48 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[A Photo Per Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gear]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Photos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=788</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[It&#8217;s been a year since I announced my intention of taking A Photo Per Day and posting the results. I&#8217;ve been cross-posting to flickr and the photos can also be seen in this A Photo Per Day Set or via the aphotoperday tag. I&#8217;m happy with the experiment &#8211; I had to keep a camera &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2007/01/01/a-year-of-photos/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "A Year of Photos"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s been a year since I announced my intention of taking <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2006/01/01/a-photo-per-day/">A Photo Per Day</a> and posting the results.</p>
<p>I&#8217;ve been cross-posting to flickr and the photos can also be seen in this <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/sets/72157594452126258/">A Photo Per Day Set</a> or via the <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/tags/aphotoperday/">aphotoperday tag</a>.</p>
<p>I&#8217;m happy with the experiment &#8211; I had to keep a camera with me almost all the time, it forced me to take photos on slow days, long days, tired days.  It made me think of interesting shots at 11 p.m. at night, and tick a box with satisfaction at 8 a.m. some mornings.  I don&#8217;t really know if my photography improved but I certainly enjoyed the process and would recommend it and consider it again.</p>
<p>Technically I did fail to take a photo <i>every</i> day, what with international timezones and a couple of forgetful evenings &#8211; but there is always a catchup photo <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2006/06/01/31st-may-06-blurry-bookshelf-v/">in the wee small hours</a>, and that&#8217;s close enough to claim victory.  </p>
<p>I&#8217;m working on a couple of new adventures in 2007 &#8211; <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/category/danika/baby-machaggis/">baby machaggis</a>, and another private enterprise that will probably not make the year.  Neither are photo projects although I imagine the <a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/tags/noodlehead">camera may come out</a> for the little one.</p>
<p>This year&#8217;s adventure was brought to you primarily by:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="http://www.nikonusa.com/template.php?goingto=dtc_options&#038;cat=1&#038;grp=2&#038;productNr=25504">Nikon Coolpix E5700</a> <b>4/5</b> &#8211; until the CCD failed this was my #1 digital camera, almost an SLR, veteran of the second half of the world trip.  Nikon replaced the CCD for free and returned the camera after a few months (two of them actually, due to a mess up, but by then my heart had been lost to the D50).</li>
<li><a href="http://www.steves-digicams.com/2004_reviews/dimagex50.html">Konica-Minolta DiMage X50</a> <b>5/5</b> &#8211; I can&#8217;t say enough great things about this little camera.  The X50 was bought as a small &#8220;Danika/party camera&#8221; so that when we went to France in 2004 she could take photos of me!  Konica-Minolta have left the camera business now (their SLR division has been bought by Sony) but if you ever see one of these little 5MP sweeties on a clearance shelf &#8211; buy it!</li>
<li><a href="http://www.nikonusa.com/template.php?goingto=dtc_options&#038;cat=1&#038;grp=2&#038;productNr=25216">Nikon D50</a> <b>4/5</b> &#8211; my second SLR, the first being a Minolta APS Vectis, I have had so much fun with this camera.  As with most SLRs it is way too complicated for me even though it is the bottom end of the digital SLR models!  Most of my shooting is on P mode, with some thumbwheel action to change speed or aperture while relying on the automatic exposure &#8211; which is how I used the E5700 too.  Unlike the E5700 the exposure is reliable (on the Coolpix I always preferred underexposing by 1/3) but it is important to do white balance properly as I generally take JPGs.  In 2007 I intend to move into the world of <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/RAW_image_format">RAW</a>, where this will be less important but I will spend more time tweaking photos at the computer as a result.   Just to play fair, the camera doesn&#8217;t get 5/5 because: a) the LCD on top doesn&#8217;t have a backlight so you can&#8217;t see the settings in the dark, b) the white balance setting isn&#8217;t shown in the viewfinder so you need to remember what you left it set on and c) at only 6MP I get pixellation in the sky for some outdoor shots around clouds etc.   Being an SLR, let&#8217;s talk lenses:
<ul>
<li>18-55mm 1:3.5-5.6 G zoom <b>3/5</b> &#8211; basic lens that come with the camera, feels a little light and cheap, but pretty fine</li>
<li>55-200mm 1:4-5.6 G zoom <b>4/5</b> &#8211; big zoom that comes with the extended camera kit, it feels better than the small lens and takes nice zoomed pictures if you don&#8217;t shake too much!  I didn&#8217;t use it as much as I thought as the 55mm bottom end is often too &#8220;zoomed&#8221; when carrying the camera around for impromptu shots</li>
<li>50mm 1:1.8 D (fixed) <b>5/5</b> &#8211; Great for everyday use, and a little reminiscent of all those great older candids that were taken by great photographers using fixed lenses.  As its faster it suits my type of photography this year (better, sharper photos in low-light with no flash), and there is also one less dial to get wrong.  I loved it</li>
</ul>
<p>The D50 has been upgraded by Nikon and is now either the D40 or D80 depending on your price-range.</li>
</ul>
<p>I was going to finish up with a favourite photo from the series, but I just can&#8217;t choose.  So &#8211; similar to the picture bar that current runs across the top of <a href="http://bluefacedpixie">bluefacedpixie</a> &#8211; here is a random &#8220;aphotoperday&#8221; from flickr:</p>
<div class="imgcenter">
<script type="text/javascript" src="http://www.flickr.com/badge_code_v2.gne?count=1&#038;display=random&#038;size=m&#038;layout=x&#038;source=user_tag&#038;user=22499205%40N00&#038;tag=aphotoperday"></script>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ever heard of Holga?</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/06/29/ever-heard-of-holga/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2006 04:45:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog This]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gear]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Photos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2006/06/29/ever-heard-of-holga/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Apparently it will save us.]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Apparently it will <a href="http://shop.lomography.com/holga/">save us</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Black and White</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/06/15/black-and-white/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2006 05:01:28 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Gear]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Photos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=402</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[A side comment on my D50 rather than the retired Coolpix 5700, not a full review: I *miss* the simple &#8220;black and white&#8221; mode on the 5700. I know that any digital shot can be made BW afterwards (I&#8217;m lo-tech and use iPhoto) but it&#8217;s post-processing work, and I love the convenience of a digital &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/06/15/black-and-white/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Black and White"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A side comment on my <a href="http://www.dpreview.com/reviews/nikond50/">D50</a> rather than the retired <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2006/01/23/run-away/">Coolpix 5700</a>, not a full review:  I *miss* the simple &#8220;black and white&#8221; mode on the 5700.  I know that any digital shot can be made BW afterwards (I&#8217;m lo-tech and use iPhoto) but it&#8217;s post-processing work, and I love the convenience of a digital camera enough <i>not</i> to want to have a <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Digital_darkroom">digital darkroom</a>.  And I still harbour the sneaking suspicion that if I&#8217;m not shooting RAW then the 5700 did some sort of &#8216;<i>stuff the extra BW bits into the JPG to make the shot look better</i>&#8216; magic that makes it&#8217;s 5MP BW shots better than a converted 6MP colour JPG.</p>
<p>But then I&#8217;m a suspicious bugger.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>8th May 06: Singlespeed Goodness</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/05/09/8th-may-06-singlespeed-goodness/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2006 03:25:06 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[A Photo Per Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cycling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Gear]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2006/05/09/8th-may-06-singlespeed-goodness/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[8th May 06: Singlespeed Goodness, originally uploaded by machaggis. Ok, I&#8217;m a bike geek. This is a freewheel hub on a Redline 9-2-5. I believe these type of photographs are called bikeporn. I also posted this. {D50, as taken, incadescent, handheld}]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="imgcenter">
	<a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/143795542/" title="Photo Per Day Linked from flickr"><img height=400 src="http://static.flickr.com/47/143795542_87e5a1cdb6.jpg" alt="8th May 06: Singlespeed Goodness" /></a></p>
<p align=center><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/143795542/" title="Link to photo on flickr">8th May 06: Singlespeed Goodness</a>, originally uploaded by <a href="http://www.flickr.com/people/machaggis/" title="Link to photographer on flickr">machaggis</a>.</p>
<p>Ok, I&#8217;m a bike geek.  This is a freewheel hub on a <a href="http://www.redlinebicycles.com/adultbikes/925.html">Redline  9-2-5</a>.<br />
I believe these type of photographs are called <a href="http://flickr.com/photos/tags/bikeporn/">bikeporn</a>.  I also posted <a href="http://flickr.com/photos/machaggis/143800049/">this</a>.<br />
{D50, as taken, incadescent, handheld}</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>First Impressions: Brooks Cascadia shoes</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2005/12/18/first-impressions-brooks-cascadia-shoes/</link>
				<comments>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2005/12/18/first-impressions-brooks-cascadia-shoes/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2005 06:34:42 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Gear]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Running]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=51</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[My new running shoes are Brooks Cascadia &#8211; my first ever trail running shoes. The shoes are ugly enough to make you puke. They are so ugly that apparently REI made Brooks produce a grey version just for them. But at least you don&#8217;t have to worry about the red/yellow look clashing with any particular &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2005/12/18/first-impressions-brooks-cascadia-shoes/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "First Impressions: Brooks Cascadia shoes"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>My new running shoes are <a href="http://www.brooksrunning.com/prod.php?k=23660&#038;p=BSI41153">Brooks Cascadia</a> &#8211; my first ever trail running shoes.   The shoes are ugly enough to make you puke.  They are so ugly that apparently <a href="http://www.rei.com">REI</a> made Brooks produce a <a href="http://www.rei.com/online/store/ProductDisplay?storeId=8000&#038;catalogId=40000008000&#038;productId=47869147&#038;parent_category_rn=4501261&#038;vcat=REI_SEARCH">grey version</a> just for them.  But at least you don&#8217;t have to worry about the red/yellow look clashing with any particular outfit &#8211; they clash with _all_ your outfits (the girl&#8217;s version is a pretty blue though).</p>
<p>I had to choose between the Brooks and and <a href="http://montrail.com/" title="montrail, can't link to the shoe">Montrail Masai</a>&#8216;s.  The Brooks are trail running shoes made by a road running company, the Masai&#8217;s are trail running shoes made by a hiking boot company.  The Masai&#8217;s were grey (a bonus) and had a good mid-foot gusset.  But they were hard under the toe, cut high in the back and I&#8217;ve been running in various Brooks since I came to the US (apart from a failed Asics experiment) so I went with the Brooks.</p>
<div class="imgcenter">
<img src="/planetdanika/uploads/scaled.240.20051217.PICT2014.JPG" width="240" height="320" alt="" />
</div>
<p>Took them for a spin around Cougar doing (what Danika and I are now calling) _Scott&#8217;s Loop_ for about 100 minutes yesterday.  Stuck my ever reliable <a href="http://www.superfeet.com">Superfeet</a> inside them as insoles. And I liked them.  Like all new shoes that fit well they feel supportive and _fast_.</p>
<p>To be honest the ground was harder than concrete (36&deg;F) and I didn&#8217;t notice anything particularly _trail runnerish_ about the shoes.  On one occasion I kicked a rock and liked the rubber toe, and they maybe gripped a little better on an uneven corner or two, but I think it&#8217;ll take more mud to determine how much better they are than my road shoes.</p>
<p>Did I say they were _fast_?</p>
<div class="imgcenter">
<img src="/planetdanika/uploads/scaled.240.20051217.PICT1987.JPG" width="240" height="180" alt="" />
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2005/12/18/first-impressions-brooks-cascadia-shoes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
							</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
