<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Rants &#8211; bluefacedpixie</title>
	<atom:link href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/category/rants/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 04:20:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.2.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>More truth, this time about underwater basket-weaving</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2011/11/30/more-truth-this-time-about-underwater-basket-weaving/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2011 04:20:12 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Geek]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rants]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2011/11/30/more-truth-this-time-about-underwater-basket-weaving/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[It&#8217;s been a while since I did any typing in bluefacedpixie but jwz&#8217;s reality call needs as many cross-links for ye-olde-google-backrub as possible. I did make a bunch of money by winning the Netscape Startup Lottery, it&#8217;s true. So did most of the early engineers. But the people who made 100x as much as the &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2011/11/30/more-truth-this-time-about-underwater-basket-weaving/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "More truth, this time about underwater basket-weaving"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s been a while since I did any typing in bluefacedpixie but <a href="http://www.jwz.org/blog/2011/11/watch-a-vc-use-my-name-to-sell-a-con/">jwz&#8217;s reality call</a> needs as many cross-links for ye-olde-google-backrub as possible.</p>
<p><i>I did make a bunch of money by winning the Netscape Startup Lottery, it&#8217;s true. So did most of the early engineers. But the people who made 100x as much as the engineers did? I can tell you for a fact that none of them slept under their desk.</i></p>
<p>So:</p>
<p><i>I recommend that you do what you love because you love doing it. If that means long hours, fantastic. If that means leaving the office by 6pm every day for your underwater basket-weaving class, also fantastic.</i></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Washing up&#8230;</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/12/31/washing-up/</link>
				<comments>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/12/31/washing-up/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2009 22:54:12 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Being Daddy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Being Scottish]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Danika]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rants]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=1291</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[..on the shores of the far side of the 2000 decade. A decade review seems to be an invitation for lists; I will try to keep it short and sweet. It seems strange that so much focus was placed on the end of the millennium (Y2K, phew), when the last ten years have been so &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/12/31/washing-up/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Washing up&#8230;"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>..on the shores of the far side of the 2000 decade.</p>
<p>A decade review  seems to be an invitation for lists; I will try to keep it short and sweet.</p>
<p>It seems strange that so much focus was placed on the end of the millennium (Y2K, phew), when the last ten years have been so full for me and so much has happened in the world.  I was in transition in 1999 as I waited for a visa to come through to let me work for an internet company in Seattle (even as the dot bomb began&#8230;), and little did I know the tradition of <a href="http://dht240.wordpress.com/2009/12/30/on-reaching-the-end-of-the-decade/">heading off for New Year&#8217;s Eve with friends</a> would be drawing to a close.</p>
<p>This year doesn&#8217;t seem that different from the last in terms of &#8220;closing out&#8221;, but decades make a nice number to chunk time by.  I&#8217;ve had the childhood decade, the teenage years, the &#8220;being adult in Scotland&#8221; decade and now&#8230; the last ten years:</p>
<p>* moving to the USA to work (and now living here on a more permanent basis)<br />
* destroying my accent<br />
* starting most sentences with &#8220;So&#8230;&#8221;<br />
* having an original iPod (deceased)<br />
* and an original iPhone (still working)<br />
* publishing random bits of stuff on the internet in a blog-thing&#8230;<br />
* taking a small trip around the world with a girl<br />
* &#8230;and marrying her&#8230;<br />
* &#8230;and becoming a family of four</p>
<p>So while this decade ends in diapers,  the next decade is going to involve a lot of homework, school runs and play.</p>
<p>See you on the other side.</p>
<p>Happy New Year.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/12/31/washing-up/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Developers hate the iPhone App Store</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/07/29/developers-hate-the-iphone-app-store/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2009 02:17:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog This]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Geek]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rants]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2009/07/29/developers-hate-the-iphone-app-store/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[And they should. It&#8217;s a disgrace. Apple semi-fanboy that I am, they should be ashamed. See also DF on this post.]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.polarbearfarm.com/blog/?p=124">And they should</a>.  It&#8217;s a disgrace.  Apple semi-fanboy that I am, they should be ashamed.  See also <a href="http://daringfireball.net/linked/2009/07/29/duncan-app-store">DF on this post</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>11 and 6</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/05/09/11-and-6/</link>
				<pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2009 08:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Rants]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2009/05/09/11-and-6/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Business travel is bad for my environmentally friendly hopes. And this doesn&#8217;t even count the free bottles in the hotel; *and* I&#8217;m not too sure I&#8217;m not short counting. And I&#8217;ve decided I&#8217;m _not_ counting gatorade bottles. But it&#8217;s a straight +4 for cups and +4 for bottles since my triumphant 7 and 2 post &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/05/09/11-and-6/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "11 and 6"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Business travel is bad for my environmentally friendly hopes.  And this doesn&#8217;t even count the free bottles in the hotel; *and* I&#8217;m not too sure I&#8217;m not short counting.  And I&#8217;ve decided I&#8217;m _not_ counting gatorade bottles.</p>
<p>But it&#8217;s a straight +4 for cups and +4 for bottles since my triumphant <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2009/04/01/7-and-2/">7 and 2</a> post at the start of April.  That&#8217;s a looong time in today&#8217;s disposable culture.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Thank Goodness for The Doctor</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/04/23/thank-goodness-for-the-doctor/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2009 05:59:00 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Rants]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Things Mac-like]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[TV]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=1210</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[I&#8217;m in the basement surrounded by LCDs and flickering lights. There are no real lights on. Unfortunately the recent trials and tribulations with the house Internet have driven me to this. Since Sunday our usually-pretty-rock-solid Internet has been playing silly buggers. I think it&#8217;s the Apple TimeCapsule Airport thing, but I&#8217;m not too sure, although &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/04/23/thank-goodness-for-the-doctor/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Thank Goodness for The Doctor"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;m in the basement surrounded by LCDs and flickering lights.  There are no real lights on.</p>
<p>Unfortunately the recent trials and tribulations with the house Internet have driven me to this.</p>
<p>Since Sunday our usually-pretty-rock-solid Internet has been playing silly buggers.  I think it&#8217;s the Apple TimeCapsule Airport thing, but I&#8217;m not too sure, although I&#8217;m pretty convinced.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s at times like this I wonder what <i>normal</i> folks do when technology doesn&#8217;t work.  And then I wish I was a <i>normal</i> person as I have just enough knowledge to be dangerous and maybe I wouldn&#8217;t be so concerned that the only solution seems to be to pull the cable out of the TimeCapsule (Apple didn&#8217;t give it an on/off switch) and plug it back in with that little pretty blue spark for about 12-hours of use before it somehow&#8230; stops working&#8230; and our backups haven&#8217;t run since last Friday&#8230;.  With all lights green and happy of course.</p>
<p>Tonight&#8217;s adventures in the attempted resolution (for I have no idea if, this time tomorrow, I won&#8217;t be using the F-word in REALLY LARGE CAPITALS) have involved downloading a lot of stuff to find out I have it already, using the cable direct from my DSL modem and doing a PPoE connection from my Mac to the outside world so I can google &#8220;TimeCapsule <strike>sucks</strike> randomly fails at simple internet&#8221;, running a full reset and reconfig on the TimeCapsule, being happy it currently works, and just waiting&#8230;.</p>
<p>However, thanks to the wonder of said Internet (when working) I have passed a small part of the evening quite wonderfully with the <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Next_Doctor">Christmas 2008</a> episode of Doctor Who.  This was following (also in a not-connected-to-the-outside-world patch) an equally (if not more so) pleasant experience with the <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Planet_of_the_Dead">Easter 2009</a> episode of Doctor Who.</p>
<p>These 2008 and 2009 specials are the swan song of the current Doctor (David Tennant, pretty damn fine), he&#8217;s retiring/due for <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Eleventh_Doctor">regeneration</a>, as is the Producer/Director <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Russell_T_Davies">Russell Davies</a> who brought Doctor Who back to the BBC.  I&#8217;m excited to see the non-Davies Who as <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php?s=doctor+who">I think the current Who-franchise is fun, cheesy and way too rah-rah-London</a> to be sustainable and will age badly but does have complete strokes of genius.</p>
<p>But the current Doctor is sensitive and caring the way the <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fifth_Doctor">Fifth Doctor</a> (aka <b><i>my Doctor</i></b> in the same way folks have <b><i>my</i> James Bond</b>) was (although many folks never gave Peter Davison the credit he deserved for that until later)  and these two episodes were good, even more so as they were isolated nuggets of goodness in a week fraught with frustration.</p>
<p><a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Planet_of_the_Dead">Planet of the Dead</a> (Easter 2009 Special): <b>4/5</b><br />
<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Next_Doctor">The Next Doctor</a> (Christmas 2008 Special): <b>3/5</b></p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>7 and 2</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/04/01/7-and-2/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2009 04:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Rants]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2009/04/01/7-and-2/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Damn. Had to buy a bottle of water from Starbuck&#8217;s today. And coffee in a paper cup. I was at the airport. Score for this year: paper cups &#8211; 7 plastic water bottles &#8211; 2]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Damn.  Had to buy a bottle of water from Starbuck&#8217;s today.  And coffee in a paper cup.  I was at the airport.</p>
<p>Score for this year:</p>
<ul>
<li>paper cups &#8211; 7</li>
<li>plastic water bottles &#8211; 2</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Installers</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/02/25/installers/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2009 22:02:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Geek]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rants]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2009/02/25/installers/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Rant, and excellent guidelines, about Installers (very important if you use software a lot, and Adobe is evil).]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Rant, and excellent guidelines, about <a href="http://www.bynkii.com/archives/2009/02/on_installers.html">Installers</a> (very important if you use software a lot, and <a href="http://blogs.adobe.com/jnack/2008/12/notes_from_installer_mgmt.html">Adobe</a> is <i>evil</i>).</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sad</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/02/04/sad/</link>
				<comments>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/02/04/sad/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2009 06:04:58 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog This]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Cycling]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rants]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2009/02/04/sad/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[At 4pm today Danika called me to check if I was alive. It seems that there was a fatal bike accident a few blocks from our house this morning. As I bike into work most days (and today) Danika had been checking the pictures to see if the bike was mine. I looked at our &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/02/04/sad/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Sad"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>At 4pm today Danika called me to check if I was alive.</p>
<p>It seems that there was a fatal bike accident a few blocks from our house this morning.  As I bike into work most days (and today) Danika had been checking the pictures to see if the bike was mine.</p>
<p>I looked at our local blog <a href="http://www.myballard.com">MyBallard</a> (*) to find some salient <a href="http://www.myballard.com/2009/02/04/accident-at-65th-st-24th-ave/">details on the story</a>, which is &#8211; of course &#8211; sad and I don&#8217;t even want to consider the what-ifs involving my mode of transportation.  What also saddens me though, is how quickly the comment stream on this story degenerates into amateur lawyermanship and random comments about bikes, riding in streets, intersection layout, the rules etc.  (160 comments at this moment, many of which are relevant and factual and very sensible and not whiny or conjectural or lawyerly).  I don&#8217;t even read them, just flinch at some of the words and the thought of how it could be.</p>
<p>Be careful out there.</p>
<p>(*) Along with many others I will claim to have had an idea of a neighbourhood blog along these lines <i>years</i> ago.  Of course I did nothing and probably saved a lot of energy in the process, lost streetcred and may not have made my fortune.  Not so the<a href="http://www.myballard.com/about/"> Geeky Swedes</a>.  Congratulations.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2009/02/04/sad/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Security Theater</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2008/12/19/security-theater/</link>
				<comments>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2008/12/19/security-theater/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2008 02:35:33 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog This]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[I'm a stranger here]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rants]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2008/12/19/security-theater/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[I didn&#8217;t blog this Atlantic article originally, but it keeps coming up in conversation. Read how a journalist deliberately and repeatedly repeats every airport security violation he can. Except without being a real terrorist of course. On another occasion, at LaGuardia, in New York, the transportation-security officer in charge of my secondary screening emptied my &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2008/12/19/security-theater/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Security Theater"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I didn&#8217;t blog this Atlantic article originally, but it keeps coming up in conversation.  <a href="http://www.theatlantic.com/doc/print/200811/airport-security">Read how a journalist</a> deliberately and repeatedly repeats <i>every airport security violation</i> he can.  Except without being a real terrorist of course.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>On another occasion, at LaGuardia, in New York, the transportation-security officer in charge of my secondary screening emptied my carry-on bag of nearly everything it contained, including a yellow, three-foot-by-four-foot Hezbollah flag, purchased at a Hezbollah gift shop in south Lebanon. The flag features, as its charming main image, an upraised fist clutching an AK-47 automatic rifle. Atop the rifle is a line of Arabic writing that reads Then surely the party of God are they who will be triumphant. The officer took the flag and spread it out on the inspection table. She finished her inspection, gave me back my flag, and told me I could go. I said, Thats a Hezbollah flag. She said, Uh-huh. Not Uh-huh, Ive been trained to recognize the symbols of anti-American terror groups, but after careful inspection of your physical person, your behavior, and your last name, Ive come to the conclusion that you are not a Bekaa Valleytrained threat to the United States commercial aviation system, but Uh-huh, Im going on break, why are you talking to me?
</p>
</blockquote>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2008/12/19/security-theater/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>I Hate Video</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2008/12/08/i-hate-video/</link>
				<comments>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2008/12/08/i-hate-video/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2008 07:01:52 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Geek]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Rants]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Things Mac-like]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=1126</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Flip Ultra (the world&#8217;s easiest video camera) + Apple MacBook Pro (very powerful laptop) + iMovie (consumer-oriented, well designed video software) + iDVD (ditto) = easy-to make home movies for Christmas. Hell, no! (repeat, LOUDER) HELL, NO! Admittedly I am using the ships-with-the-computer versions of iMovie and iDVD (iMovie 6 and iDVD &#8217;06 I believe) &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2008/12/08/i-hate-video/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "I Hate Video"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><a href="http://www.amazon.com/Flip-Video-Ultra-Camcorder-60-Minutes/dp/B000V1PXMI/ref=pd_bbs_sr_1?ie=UTF8&#038;s=electronics&#038;qid=1228805777&#038;sr=8-1&#038;tag=ballardcorner-20">Flip Ultra</a> (the world&#8217;s easiest video camera) + Apple <a href="http://www.amazon.com/Apple-MB133LL-15-4-inch-Processor-SuperDrive/dp/B0013FLU96/ref=pd_bbs_sr_2?ie=UTF8&#038;s=electronics&#038;qid=1228805842&#038;sr=8-2&#038;tag=ballardcorner-20">MacBook Pro</a> (very powerful laptop) + <a href="http://www.amazon.com/Apple-MB015Z-A-iLife-08/dp/B000BX5JQG/ref=pd_bbs_sr_4?ie=UTF8&#038;s=software&#038;qid=1228805882&#038;sr=8-4&#038;tag=ballardcorner-20">iMovie</a> (consumer-oriented, well designed video software) + <a href="http://www.amazon.com/Apple-MB015Z-A-iLife-08/dp/B000BX5JQG/ref=pd_bbs_sr_4?ie=UTF8&#038;s=software&#038;qid=1228805882&#038;sr=8-4&#038;tag=ballardcorner-20">iDVD</a> (ditto) = easy-to make home movies for Christmas.</p>
<p><b>Hell, no!</b></p>
<p>(repeat, LOUDER)</p>
<p><b><large>HELL, NO!</large></b></p>
<p>Admittedly I am using the ships-with-the-computer versions of iMovie and iDVD (iMovie 6 and iDVD &#8217;06 I believe) as opposed to the iLife &#8217;08 versions; but this is hardly an advert for spending money on Apple software.</p>
<p>To save me having to type lots of expletives, or Karima-level exclamation points, the answer is <b>NO, F**K NO!</b>.   72 hours in, still fighting.</p>
<p>One result:</p>
<p><code>grandvizier:~ gordon$ cat ~/scripts/every-x-do-y<br />
</code><code>#!/bin/bash<br />
</code><code><br />
</code><code>while true; do $2; sleep $1; done<br />
</code><code><br />
</code><code>grandvizier:~ gordon$ cat ~/scripts/kill-syslogd<br />
</code><code>#!/bin/sh<br />
</code><code>echo "sudo required"<br />
</code><code>sudo launchctl stop com.apple.syslogd<br />
</code><code>sudo rm -f /var/log/asl.* /var/log/system.log*<br />
</code><code>sudo launchctl start com.apple.syslogd<br />
</code><code><br />
</code><code>grandvizier:~ gordon$ sudo every-x-do-y 300 kill-syslogd<br />
</code></p>
<p>For the geeks amongst us, this is my sledgehammer to the <a href="http://discussions.apple.com/thread.jspa?messageID=8267806">discussions.apple.com</a> solution for this problem (QT hates badly encoded movies and is coded by a three-year -old):</p>
<p><code>Dec  8 22:22:16 grandvizier [0x0-0x2d02d].com.apple.iDVD[326]: OQT_MovieImport: fseek_store: tried to seek to 7686744513496; outside of file</code></p>
<p>So, if you get a shiny disk with Lucy on it, and it actually works &#8211; it was made with blood and hours.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2008/12/08/i-hate-video/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
							</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
