<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Toys &#8211; bluefacedpixie</title>
	<atom:link href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/category/reviews/toys/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2007 17:22:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.2.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>The Kindle and Digital Reading</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2007/11/20/the-kindle-and-digital-reading/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2007 17:22:08 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Toys]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=957</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[I&#8217;ve skirted around ebook readers for a while especially the Sony eReader, and ironically enough, just succumbed as my old Amazon colleagues finally released the Kindle. A very different device &#8211; not so much a static reading device as a wirelessly-tethered access-point for Amazon sold books and content. Along with the fact it&#8217;s butt-ugly compared &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2007/11/20/the-kindle-and-digital-reading/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "The Kindle and Digital Reading"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I&#8217;ve skirted around ebook readers for a while especially the <a href="www.amazon.com/E-reader-Portable-Silver-E-book-Approx/dp/B000WPXQ2M?tag=ballardcorner-20">Sony eReader</a>, and ironically enough, just succumbed as my old Amazon colleagues finally released the <a href="http://www.amazon.com/Amazon-com-kindle/dp/B000FI73MA?tag=ballardcorner-20">Kindle</a>.   A very different device &#8211; not so much a static reading device as a wirelessly-tethered access-point for Amazon sold books and content.</p>
<p>Along with the fact it&#8217;s butt-ugly compared to the Sony gorgeousness (industrial design and v2 can always fix that), it has generally gone down badly in the press for the lack of open formats (no PDF, presumably this can be updated by software later), aggressive DRM, pricing, blog pricing and crazy terms and conditions (<super>þ</super>).</p>
<p>By far the best synopsis of the perfect storm of bad ideas that reach a conclusion in the Kindle offering is Mark Pilgrim&#8217;s <a href="http://diveintomark.org/archives/2007/11/19/the-future-of-reading">The Future of Reading (A Play in Six Parts)</a>.  Read this, and then reach for your copy of <a href="http://www.amazon.com/1984/dp/B000FA5U1E?tag=ballardcorner-20">1984</a>.</p>
<p>(þ) Amazon&#8217;s MP3 store also has steep terms and conditions (presumably to offset the non-DRM format of their music files) reducing your normal conditions for even digital music copyright quite drastically.  Remember, if you accept it, then you are bound by it, regardless of rights.</p>
<p><em>Update:</em> Concerned that this read too negatively, especially as I&#8217;m really just cross-posting Pilgrim&#8217;s rant, I thought I&#8217;d weigh the scales with this balanced &#8220;wait it out&#8221; from <a href="http://www.37signals.com/svn/posts/712-kindle-ignites-the-flames">Signal vs. Noise</a>:</p>
<blockquote>
<p>Kindle isnt the first eBook reader, but its the first portable bookstore. Thats novel. A book in 60 seconds whenever I want it at used-bookstore prices. And the daily push newspaper feature sounds like one hell of a bonus. I love getting the paper, but I hate getting the paper. What a complete waste of resources just so I can get yesterdays news. I like that theres some genuinely new thinking behind Kindle. We should embrace this, not tear it to shreds before it even has a chance.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Personally I love the idea of a good eReader &#8211; too often the fantasy books I prefer clock in at 1000 pages and are large-format paperbacks.  It&#8217;s awkward to take one or two of these anywhere (especially totting a baby).  The whole DRM and lock-in is a big issue in the industry which is different from the iPod scenario &#8211; I can&#8217;t go to my bookshelf and &#8220;rip&#8221; my favourite books &#8211; I have to buy new ones from somewhere, and it would be nice to share.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mmm, tastes like chocolate apples</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2007/08/07/mmm-tastes-like-chocolate-apples/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2007 05:21:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Being Daddy]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Photos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Things Mac-like]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Toys]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2007/08/07/mmm-tastes-like-chocolate-apples/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Mmm, tastes like chocolate apples, originally uploaded by machaggis. a) The unwritten feature of the iPhone; b) When the girl starts to teeth, everything is at risk.]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="imgcenter">
	<a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/1047512434/" title="Linked from flickr"><img width=400 src="http://farm2.static.flickr.com/1164/1047512434_c16c069174.jpg" alt="Mmm, tastes like chocolate apples" /></a></p>
<p align=center><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/1047512434/" title="Link to photo on flickr">Mmm, tastes like chocolate apples</a>, originally uploaded by <a href="http://www.flickr.com/people/machaggis/" title="Link to photographer on flickr">machaggis</a>.</p>
<p>a) The unwritten feature of the iPhone;<br />
b) When the girl starts to teeth, everything is at risk.</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>3rd Oct 06: Danika&#8217;s New Toy</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/10/05/3rd-oct-06-danikas-new-toy/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2006 06:13:21 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[A Photo Per Day]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Toys]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2006/10/05/3rd-oct-06-danikas-new-toy/</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[3rd Oct 06: Danika&#8217;s New Toy, originally uploaded by machaggis. It&#8217;s not everyday a new electronic toy arrives in Chez Waddell and doesn&#8217;t belong to me. After months of procrastination and waiting, Danika&#8217;s sexy new phone arrived. A Walkman W810i, it does all sorts of things. Even the name walkman triggers nostalgic memories. {D50, as &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/10/05/3rd-oct-06-danikas-new-toy/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "3rd Oct 06: Danika&#8217;s New Toy"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<div class="imgcenter">
	<a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/262029683/" title="Linked from flickr"><img width=400 src="http://static.flickr.com/117/262029683_41d5d46af7.jpg" alt="3rd Oct 06: Danika's New Toy" /></a></p>
<p align=center><a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/machaggis/262029683/" title="Link to photo on flickr">3rd Oct 06: Danika&#8217;s New Toy</a>, originally uploaded by <a href="http://www.flickr.com/people/machaggis/" title="Link to photographer on flickr">machaggis</a>.</p>
<p>It&#8217;s not everyday a new electronic toy arrives in Chez Waddell and doesn&#8217;t belong to me.  After months of procrastination and waiting, Danika&#8217;s sexy new phone arrived.  A Walkman W810i, it does all sorts of things.<br />
Even the name <i>walkman</i> triggers nostalgic memories.<br />
{D50, as taken, handheld}</p>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ruminations on camera buying</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/01/30/ruminations-on-camera-buying/</link>
				<comments>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/01/30/ruminations-on-camera-buying/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2006 07:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Photos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Toys]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=131</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[I shopped and bought (well ordered) a new camera this weekend. There&#8217;s lots of ramblings after the more. As narrated in &#8220;Run Away&#8220;, my Nikon 5700 died after 3 years and I decided to replace it quickly in order to have a camera for our upcoming Mexico vacation. We do have another digital camera: the &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/01/30/ruminations-on-camera-buying/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Ruminations on camera buying"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>I shopped and bought (well ordered) a new camera this weekend.  There&#8217;s lots of ramblings after the more. <span id="more-131"></span></p>
<p>As narrated in &#8220;<a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2006/01/23/run-away/">Run Away</a>&#8220;, my <a href="http://www.nikonusa.com/template.php?cat=1&#038;grp=2&#038;productNr=25504">Nikon 5700</a> died after 3 years and I decided to replace it quickly in order to have a camera for our upcoming Mexico vacation.  We do have another digital camera: the faithful Konica Minolta Dimage <a href="http://konicaminolta.com/products/consumer/digital_camera/dimage/dimage-x50/">X50</a>.  Even though Konica Minolta have recently announced they are <a href="http://www.popphoto.com/article.asp?section_id=5&#038;article_id=1697">exiting the camera business</a>  and there is a newer <a href="http://konicaminolta.com/products/consumer/digital_camera/dimage/dimage-x60/">X60</a> out there I recommend this camera as a point-and-shoot, but as it&#8217;s got a few bashes and occasionally suffers from photo-blur itself it doesn&#8217;t stand up as our main camera.  Even though it&#8217;s been doing all of the heavy lifting for the <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2006/01/01/snowboard-girl/">snowboarding</a> and <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/category/photos/a-photo-per-day/">aphotoperday</a> shots this year.</p>
<p>I decided it was time to go DSLR, but the playing field is competitive with not a bad camera in the <a href="http://www.popphoto.com/article.asp?section_id=2&#038;article_id=1708&#038;print_page=y">2005 DSLR pack</a>.</p>
<p>The two cameras I&#8217;ve had some hands on with are the Canon Rebel XT (Ed&#8217;s camera) which is small, a little confusing and has <i>great</i> 8MP resolution and the Nikon D70 which Philipa has.  I think I like the D70 (<a href="http://www.popphoto.com/article.asp?section_id=2&#038;article_id=1156&#038;print_page=y">Camera of the year 2004</a>) better but it looks like this camera is getting old and the D50 has most of its features for a much better price, is slightly smaller, and comes with an option of <b>2</b> kit lenses &#8211; 18-55 and 55-200!  The 6MP doesn&#8217;t worry me too much, as the 5MP of the 5700 and X50 have given me 18&#215;30 posters of my favourite frog without anything to worry about.</p>
<p>I did have a quick look at replacing the 5700 with an <a href="http://www.popphoto.com/article.asp?section_id=2&#038;article_id=1709&#038;print_page=y">EVF camera</a>  and in general they have built-in lenses, great features (image stabilization) and tons of pixels.  But I&#8217;m hoping that the SLR will have more long-term benefit, better manual focus (could never rely on the 5700&#8217;s EVF) and in general be <b>more fun</b>.</p>
<p>So I had a look at a bundle of camera&#8217;s (liked the Pentax *ist DL in person, was offered a great deal on the very heavy Konica Minolta Maxuum 5D with image stabilization) and plumped for the Nikon D50 (<a href="http://www.popphoto.com/article.asp?section_id=2&#038;article_id=1505&#038;print_page=y">pophoto</a>, <a href="http://www.dpreview.com/reviews/nikond50/">dpreview</a>).</p>
<p>Online purchasing is definitely the way to go though: <a href="http://adorama.com">adorama.com</a> (authorized Nikon dealer) has great official prices and no tax (not being in WA) saving almost a couple of hundred dollars in total, so I placed the order with them hoping it&#8217;ll be here before the end of the week.  Various other sundries are required of course: a new digital SD card, batteries, and UV filters; but I&#8217;ll pick them up as required over the next few weeks.</p>
<p>I&#8217;ll let you know how the camera is once it arrives.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/01/30/ruminations-on-camera-buying/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
							</item>
		<item>
		<title>Run Away</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/01/23/run-away/</link>
				<comments>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/01/23/run-away/#comments</comments>
				<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2006 06:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Photos]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Toys]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=112</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[After over three years of pretty faithful service and hundreds of great photos my Nikon 5700 has just freaked out. Although I got it serviced and a few new gears put in last October the digital/focus/CCD part of it seems to have started suddenly to fail. I can&#8217;t remember dropping it, and it was taking &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/01/23/run-away/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Run Away"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>After over three years of pretty faithful service and hundreds of great photos my <a href="http://www.nikonusa.com/template.php?cat=1&#038;grp=2&#038;productNr=25504">Nikon 5700 </a> has just freaked out.   Although I got it serviced and a few new gears put in last October the digital/focus/CCD part of it seems to have started suddenly to fail.  I can&#8217;t remember dropping it, and it was taking good pictures on the <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2006/01/16/16th-jan-06-more-coffee-love/">16th</a>.  As today&#8217;s <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/2006/01/23/23rd-jan-06-avocado-pit/">Avocado picture</a> shows, all is no longer well in the state of Denmark.</p>
<div class="imgcenter"><img src="/planetdanika/uploads/scaled.240.20060123.DSCN6193.JPG" width="240" height="180" alt="" /></div>
<p>This picture of our dining table also looks quite arty.  I was feeling brave though and thought maybe something had just got loose so decided to open the camera up.   One look was enough:</p>
<div class="imgcenter"><img src="/planetdanika/uploads/scaled.240.20060123.PICT2377.JPG" width="240" height="180" alt="" /></div>
<p>Wise men run away.  I quickly put the beast back together again, although the screws were pretty small.  Here&#8217;s half of them:</p>
<div class="imgcenter"><img src="/planetdanika/uploads/scaled.240.20060123.PICT2379.JPG" width="240" height="180" alt="" /></div>
<p>Not quite sure what I&#8217;m going to do, as the repair cost last October was about 1/3 the price of the whole camera and apparently these things don&#8217;t last forever.  Maybe I need to start thinking Digital SLR, especially as my little <a href="http://konicaminolta.com/products/consumer/digital_camera/dimage/dimage-x50/">Dimage X50</a>  (which took the legible pictures) is bashed, occasionally takes similar looking pictures and is falling apart slightly.  At least I remember dropping <i>that</i> one &#8211; several times.  But I need a camera for <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/index.php/category/photos/a-photo-per-day/">a photo per day</a>.  </p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/01/23/run-away/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
							</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
