<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Travel &#8211; bluefacedpixie</title>
	<atom:link href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/category/travel/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2013 03:30:35 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.2.4</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Down jacket saves the day! &#8211; 20th March 2003</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2013/03/13/down-jacket-saves-the-day-20th-march-2003/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2013 03:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[master]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=1545</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[(Being a re-post of a ten-year old Yahoo groups newsletter update) [Danika&#8217;s Family Home, Buffalo, NY, USA] (g: we return to the US, after many newsletters from other countries) We finally made it back to the US of A. Our adventures in exotic lands have ended. It was cold in Buffalo when we arrived &#8211; &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2013/03/13/down-jacket-saves-the-day-20th-march-2003/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Down jacket saves the day! &#8211; 20th March 2003"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><i>(Being a re-post of a ten-year old Yahoo groups newsletter update)</i></p>
<p>[Danika&#8217;s Family Home, Buffalo, NY, USA]</p>
<p>(g: we return to the US, after many newsletters from other countries)</p>
<p>We finally made it back to the US of A. Our adventures in exotic lands have ended. It was cold in Buffalo when we arrived &#8211; three days after sunbathing on the beach in Manly we were in 12 degree weather. And this time it was in Fahrenheit (-11 Centigrade!).</p>
<p>Our trip home was uneventful: China Air took us from Sydney to Taipei, Taiwan and onwards to JFK before we finally reached Buffalo. We spent almost a day in Taipei but didn&#8217;t see much except the National Palace Museum (which was pretty cool) and a lot of signs in Chinese.</p>
<p>Since arriving in Buffalo we&#8217;ve been adjusting through &#8216;post-trip blues&#8217;. We&#8217;ve visited Danika&#8217;s friends in Buffalo, been to a St. Patrick&#8217;s Day parade and stuffed our faces at the St. Joseph&#8217;s Day table in the nearby school.</p>
<p>We&#8217;re starting the mammoth task of working out how to get married this year (locations, dates etc.). We&#8217;re also starting to look for some form of gainful employment <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/1f642.png" alt="🙂" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></p>
<p>Our plans are ill-defined just now. We&#8217;ll probably hang in Buffalo until we can move Seattle-ways again, and if that doesn&#8217;t work out then we&#8217;ll look at other options.</p>
<p>Until we have something exciting to say this will be our last newsletter for a while (although a website may be coming soon), but feel free to contact us in Buffalo. We&#8217;re at (206)&#8230;., gordon@m&#8230;, danika@m&#8230; and just email us for the postal address.</p>
<p>Thanks for listening,</p>
<p>G &#038; D</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ten Years Ago</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2013/03/07/ten-years-ago/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 06:40:53 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[master]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=1541</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[We finished our trip around the world. A small time later I put together this movie slideshow, which I have resurrected from the original machaggis.net for our viewing pleasure. The quality is both amateurish and appropriate for it&#8217;s time. But it&#8217;s a blast, enjoy in all it&#8217;s 640&#215;480 glory.]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We finished our trip around the world.  A small time later I put together this movie slideshow, which I have resurrected from the original machaggis.net for our viewing pleasure.  The quality is both amateurish and appropriate for it&#8217;s time.  But it&#8217;s <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/world.mov">a blast</a>, enjoy in all it&#8217;s 640&#215;480 glory.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<enclosure url="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/world.mov" length="10895453" type="video/quicktime" />
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>5th March 2003 &#8211; Buffalo, NY</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2013/03/07/5th-march-2003-buffalo-ny/</link>
				<pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 06:37:35 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[master]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=1537</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[Day 241. Two Hundred and Forty One Days. Not even a year. And we return to the USA and &#8220;finish&#8221; our travelling adventure. From the last day in Australia we head to America by detouring to a final Asian stop in Taiwan. Aided by a 22 (I think) hour layover we basically had enough time &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2013/03/07/5th-march-2003-buffalo-ny/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "5th March 2003 &#8211; Buffalo, NY"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Day 241.  Two Hundred and Forty One Days.  Not even a year.  And we return to the USA and &#8220;finish&#8221; our travelling adventure.   From the last day in Australia we head to America by detouring to a final Asian stop in Taiwan.  Aided by a 22 (I think) hour layover we basically had enough time to sleep in a hotel and have a trip through Taipei to do the massive National Palace Museum.  And then we were back on a plane.  We overnighted in a dismal wet NYC in a generic airport Marriot and then had a pleasant Jet Blue flight back to Buffalo.</p>
<p>Our last official newsletter came out on the 20th of March that year, by which time we were a few weeks into settling back into an &#8220;untethered in America&#8221; routine.  I&#8217;ll post it in a couple of days.</p>
<p>Although our trip was over we were not quite done, and even the 20th of March update did not foresee the amount of things we would do before we settled into what would become our Ballard, Seattle, life for what has now been ten years.   In the remainder of 2003 we stayed in Buffalo for weeks (in the winter!), we made machaggis.net, Danika and the female Bondi&#8217;s headed off to Sicily, I drove across the USA in 4 days to take the Beetle back to Seattle, I re-upped with Amazon, I worked in the UK for the summer, I dealt with the INS (again), we returned to Seattle, got married (back in Buffalo) and we bought a little house in Ballard.   Our tumbleweed didn&#8217;t stop on March 5th, more like December 13th.  But we settled.  For now.</p>
<table width=100% cellpadding=1 cellspacing=4 border=0>
<tr>
<th align=center valign=top width=35>day</th>
<th align=center valign=top width=100>date</th>
<th align=center valign=top width=35%>overnight</th>
<th align=center valign=top>activity</th>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>239</td>
<td align=center valign=top>3-Mar-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Airport Hotel, Taipei, Taiwan</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Fly to Taiwan</p>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>240</td>
<td align=center valign=top>4-Mar-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Marriot Hotel, JFK, NYC, NY</td>
<td align=center valign=top>National Palace Museum, Taiwan. Fly to America, our March 4th is 38 hours long!</p>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>241</td>
<td align=center valign=top>5-Mar-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Buffalo, NY</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Jet Blue from JFK to BUF. Day 241. The adventure ends.<br />
</table>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Buffalo wings us home &#8211; 2nd March 2003</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2013/03/03/buffalo-wings-us-home-2nd-march-2003/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 05:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[master]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=1535</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[(Being a re-post of a ten-year old Yahoo groups newsletter update) [Andy &#038; Jane&#8217;s Abode, Manly, Australia] Today we leave for the USA, we&#8217;ll be in New York tomorrow and Buffalo on Wednesday! It&#8217;s a bit more complicated than that due to time zones, but that&#8217;s the idea. We&#8217;ve enjoyed our short layover in Australia &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2013/03/03/buffalo-wings-us-home-2nd-march-2003/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Buffalo wings us home &#8211; 2nd March 2003"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><i>(Being a re-post of a ten-year old Yahoo groups newsletter update)</i></p>
<p>[Andy &#038; Jane&#8217;s Abode, Manly, Australia]</p>
<p>Today we leave for the USA, we&#8217;ll be in New York tomorrow and Buffalo on Wednesday! It&#8217;s a bit more complicated than that due to time zones, but that&#8217;s the idea.</p>
<p>We&#8217;ve enjoyed our short layover in Australia &#8211; getting back to the surf and beach of Manly has been great. This is especially true as our attempts to shake the rain clouds of New Zealand weren&#8217;t as successful as we would have wished. Our last week in Kiwi-land involved us hiking the Abel Tasman trail in the dark and rain (and wading rivers), travelling to Wellington to see the Lord of the Rings Exhibition and the Two Towers movie (again), visiting the `tres cool&#8217; art deco township of Napier, tasting wine in Hawkes Bay and visiting old friends&#8230;. By a great chance, Gordon&#8217;s university friends Gary and Gil, and their new addition Holly, were in Hamilton. Gary is doing a research and teaching sabbatical at the University of Waikato and we hung out with them for a couple of days as the rain poured down once more. Gordon is re-invigorated with techy-fever now, which should help when he starts to apply for new jobs in Seattle.</p>
<p>This weekend we arrived in Australia from New Zealand in a blaze of sunshine, which went down very well with both of us! We caught up on some badly overdue sights in Sydney (the Australian Museum &#8211; where Andrew works &#8211; and the botanical gardens), went on a couple of walks, Gordon went scuba diving (for the first time in a looong time), we swam, lay on the beach and went to the Gay and Lesbian Mardi Gras. This was a fabulously entertaining event: dancing troops, happy crowds, ticker tape, floats and Thai food afterwards! We also had our last Aussie BBQ, this time on the deck in Manly &#8211; thanks Andy &#038; Jane!</p>
<p>And that&#8217;s that, two hundred and thirty nine (239) days, twelve countries (thirteen after today), one engagement, several pizzas and a glass or two of wine later&#8230;. we&#8217;re heading back to the US of A. Hope to see all our America-based friends soon, and we&#8217;ll send our next exciting instalment from the town of snow and Buffalo wings.</p>
<p>G &#038; D</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>2nd March 2003 &#8211; Manly, Australia</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2013/03/03/2nd-march-2003-manly-australia/</link>
				<pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2013 05:16:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[master]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=1532</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[We leave NZ and return to Australia. At long last Danika meets Andy and Jane (and vice versa) and we reside once more in Chez Donnelly-Allison in Manly. We meet up again with Cameron, have a crazy run around time in Sydney, taking advantage of Andy &#038; Jane&#8217;s insider knowledge. Andy drags me out scuba &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2013/03/03/2nd-march-2003-manly-australia/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "2nd March 2003 &#8211; Manly, Australia"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We leave NZ and return to Australia.  At long last Danika meets Andy and Jane (and vice versa) and we reside once more in Chez Donnelly-Allison in Manly.  We meet up again with Cameron, have a crazy run around time in Sydney, taking advantage of Andy &#038; Jane&#8217;s insider knowledge.  Andy drags me out scuba diving, for the first time in a very, very long time (certificate validity, *cough*, *cough* etc); I almost max out in an unrelated boogy boarding rip-tide incident and we go for what would be a nice hike except for Andy&#8217;s knowledge of things that can sting, maim, hurt and occasionally kill you putting us somewhat on guard.  Oh yeah, and there were forest fires approaching Sydney. All of that served to distract us from the upcoming final leg of the trip.  Back to the USA, which is going to be, once more, home &#8211; somewhere.</p>
<table width=100% cellpadding=1 cellspacing=4 border=0>
<tr>
<th align=center valign=top width=35>day</th>
<th align=center valign=top width=100>date</th>
<th align=center valign=top width=35%>overnight</th>
<th align=center valign=top>activity</th>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>234</td>
<td align=center valign=top>26-Feb-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Gary &#038; Gil&#8217;s, Hamilton, New Zealand</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Hang out in the rain in Hamilton, have pizza. Visit the University of Waikato.</p>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>235</td>
<td align=center valign=top>27-Feb-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>A &#038; J, Manly, Australia</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Fly back to Sydney.</p>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>236</td>
<td align=center valign=top>28-Feb-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>A &#038; J, Manly, Australia</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Packed :), went to Australian Museum (where Andy works)</p>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>237</td>
<td align=center valign=top>1-Mar-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>A &#038; J, Manly, Australia</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Andy&#8217;s Birthday, went scuba, Gay &#038; Lesbian march.</p>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>238</td>
<td align=center valign=top>2-Mar-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>A &#038; J, Manly, Australia</td>
<td align=center valign=top>South Head, Sydney, Doyles fish and chips, met Cameron &#038; Liz for lunch, beach, Tuna steak BBQ<br />
</table>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>21st February 2003 &#8211; Bark Bay Hut, Abel Tasman, New Zealand</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2013/02/22/21st-february-2003-bark-bay-hut-abel-tasman-new-zealand/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 05:45:01 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=1523</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[As a Scotsman (Glasgow = 49&#8243; of rain a year (one inch less than NYC)) and a resident of Seattle (37.5&#8243; of rain a year, but let&#8217;s not talk about the clouds) I really shouldn&#8217;t be *that* annoyed that we had a week or two of rain-drenched adventure. After all New Zealand is a not &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2013/02/22/21st-february-2003-bark-bay-hut-abel-tasman-new-zealand/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "21st February 2003 &#8211; Bark Bay Hut, Abel Tasman, New Zealand"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>As a Scotsman (Glasgow = <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Glasgow#Climate">49&#8243; of rain a year</a> (one inch less than NYC)) and a resident of Seattle (<a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Seattle#Climate">37.5&#8243; of rain a year</a>, but let&#8217;s not talk about the <b>clouds</b>) I really shouldn&#8217;t be *that* annoyed that we had a week or two of rain-drenched adventure.  After all New Zealand is a not disimilar temperate climate; it&#8217;s a long thin island in a big ocean full of clouds; it&#8217;s very *green* which means it must *rain* but after our awesome Kepler Track hike we paid our dues.   Running from rain in the south glaciers we headed to <a href="http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arthur%27s_Pass">Arthur&#8217;s Pass</a> (Pop. 54) only to be flooded out again &#8211; our new tent was not a boat!!</p>
<p>But we carried on, with panache.</p>
<p>Day 229 finds us bunking in bunk beds, wet, after arriving late, on the very awesome Abel Tasman Track in NZ.  It&#8217;s a strange country where it has a bundle of great hikes, it advertizes them and people (and tourists!) hike them.  And yet they are not overcrowded or subject to lottery etc (I&#8217;m looking at you Mt. Rainier; Alpine Lakes et al).  The advantages of a great ratio of population:awesomeness (the US has this as well but it&#8217;s so dang large that the ratio of local population:local awesomeness sometimes overwhelms the awesomeness).  And yes, I use the word awesome a lot now.</p>
<p>But 229 days into the trip, as <a href="http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=1521">our last newsletter notes</a>, we were starting to think of THE END.  The clock was ticking.  The USA was approaching.  Our time in NZ, and Australia, and parts beyond, was starting to become very, very finite.</p>
<p>(On a side note, I have no recollection of &#8220;Puzzle World in Wanaka&#8221; and need to talk to Danika about that when she gets off an awful I99N snarl up)</p>
<table width=100% cellpadding=1 cellspacing=4 border=0>
<tr>
<th align=center valign=top width=35>day</th>
<th align=center valign=top width=100>date</th>
<th align=center valign=top width=35%>overnight</th>
<th align=center valign=top>activity</th>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>221</td>
<td align=center valign=top>13-Feb-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Iris Burn Hut, Kepler Track, New Zealand</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Ace hiking day, lunch at Hanging Valley</p>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>222</td>
<td align=center valign=top>14-Feb-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Moturau hut, Kepler Track, New Zealand	</td>
<td align=center valign=top> and beach cricket</p>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>223</td>
<td align=center valign=top>15-Feb-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Te Anau, New Zealand</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Rainbow Reach, beers and hang out</p>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>224</td>
<td align=center valign=top>16-Feb-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Franz Josef, New Zealand</td>
<td align=center valign=top>PuzzleWorld in Wanaka</p>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>225</td>
<td align=center valign=top>17-Feb-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Franz Josef, New Zealand</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Heli-hike cancelled :(, did half day glacier hike instead</p>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>226</td>
<td align=center valign=top>18-Feb-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Arthur&#8217;s Pass, New Zealand</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Rained out, went to Arthur&#8217;s Pass via Pancake Rocks, rained more</p>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>227</td>
<td align=center valign=top>19-Feb-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Nelson, New Zealand</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Rained out again, watched Just Married, Nelson was a little sunny</p>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>228</td>
<td align=center valign=top>20-Feb-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Marahau, New Zealand</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Did we do nothing? Kinda&#8230; sight seeing and stuff</p>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>229</td>
<td align=center valign=top>21-Feb-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Bark Bay Hut, Abel Tasman Track, New Zealand</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Aquataxi to Totoranui, hike in rain and through rivers<br />
</table>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wetter than a Scottish summer. &#8211; 19th February 2003</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2013/02/22/wetter-than-a-scottish-summer-19th-february-2003/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2013 05:21:19 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=1521</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[(Being a re-post of a ten-year old Yahoo groups newsletter update) [Boots-Off Internet, Nelson, New Zealand] We&#8217;ve spent the last week hiking our butts off and getting completely soaked, though not at the same time. We&#8217;ve experienced our worst weather yet in New Zealand and discovered that our new tent is NOT waterproof from below &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2013/02/22/wetter-than-a-scottish-summer-19th-february-2003/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "Wetter than a Scottish summer. &#8211; 19th February 2003"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><i>(Being a re-post of a ten-year old Yahoo groups newsletter update)</i></p>
<p>[Boots-Off Internet, Nelson, New Zealand]</p>
<p>We&#8217;ve spent the last week hiking our butts off and getting completely soaked, though not at the same time. We&#8217;ve experienced our worst weather yet in New Zealand and discovered that our new tent is NOT waterproof from below when sitting in a field three inches deep in storm rain! The rain has put a little bit of a dint in our plans: hopes to take a helicopter ride and full-on glacier hike were ditched, and we took rather a large detour to a place called &#8216;Arthur&#8217;s Pass&#8217; only to have to leave again due to the blasted rain <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/12.0.0-1/72x72/1f642.png" alt="🙂" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> Fortunately, the rain has ceased for the time being, and we managed to do some fun stuff before and during!</p>
<p>Last week we went on a cruise and kayak in the Milford Sound fiord, we overnighted on the boat and the difference between the windy and rainy evening and the blue-sky morning was a wonder to see. We followed this by tackling our first more-than-one-day &#8220;Great Walk&#8221; in NZ &#8211; the Kepler Track. It took us four days (though we could have done it quicker) and was quite spectacular. There were fiords, alpine crossings, mountain peaks (Mt. Luxmore) and enchanting forests. We had to carry food and big packs, but stayed in excellent NZ huts so we didn&#8217;t have to carry the big tent! We befriended quite a few characters on the walk and even managed to watch some beach cricket. All in all, we thought it was such great fun that we&#8217;re going to do another Great Walk tomorrow. This time, we&#8217;re doing the Abel Tasman track which is mostly coastal and includes lots of beaches and some beach crossings at low tide only! We plan to do this walk a little faster &#8211; just two days, just as well as our ferry leaves the South Island the same day we finish the track!</p>
<p>After the beauty of the Fiordland area we drove up the west coast in some damp and wild weather. Although this put paid to our planned &#8216;treat&#8217; of a helicopter hike on the Franz Josef or Fox glaciers we did go for a guided hike on the Franz Josef glacier anyway. This was good fun, despite a little rain (snow would have looked nicer) and was not near as cold as you may have thought! That night was when the storm rain started that plagued us for the next few days, but last night we finally spent a dry night in the tent and woke up to sunshine and clear skies.</p>
<p>We&#8217;re chilling in Nelson &#8211; fully drying out from recent days and catching up on a few chores. Saturday night, we return to the North Island for a last few days before we head back to Australia. We&#8217;re considering this the start of the &#8216;journey home&#8217;, after a weekend in Australia we start the several-day trek to Buffalo where we&#8217;ll consider the main part of the trip over. We&#8217;re happy and sad to be considering our return &#8211; we&#8217;re not really done travelling but unless we want to do a lot of fruit-picking, our time and budget is up!</p>
<p>Here&#8217;s to being in Buffalo in two weeks!</p>
<p>Danika &#038; Gordon</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>12th February 2003 &#8211; Kepler Track, New Zealand</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2013/02/13/12th-february-2003-kepler-track-new-zealand/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 05:49:24 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=1518</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[This week in New Zealand was very much a Lord of the Rings tour although the two days nominally &#8220;not a main sight&#8221; were spent in Te Anau which ranks as one of my favourite named towns in the whole wide world. We also hiked up Ben Lomond, in much better condition than the last &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2013/02/13/12th-february-2003-kepler-track-new-zealand/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "12th February 2003 &#8211; Kepler Track, New Zealand"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>This week in New Zealand was very much a Lord of the Rings tour although the two days nominally &#8220;not a main sight&#8221; were spent in Te Anau which ranks as one of my favourite named towns in the whole wide world.  We also hiked up Ben Lomond, in much better condition than the last time we tackled a mountain of that name and start the <a href="http://www.doc.govt.nz/parks-and-recreation/tracks-and-walks/fiordland/eastern-fiordland/kepler-track/">Kepler Track</a> Great Walk after a gorgeous, if wet, overnight on a boat in Milford Sound.</p>
<table width=100% cellpadding=1 cellspacing=4 border=0>
<tr>
<th align=center valign=top width=35>day</th>
<th align=center valign=top width=100>date</th>
<th align=center valign=top width=35%>overnight</th>
<th align=center valign=top>activity</th>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>216</td>
<td align=center valign=top>8-Feb-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Queenstown, New Zealand</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Lord of the Rings sights (Remarkables, Dimrill Dale, Wizards Vale, Isengard, Glenorchy, Paradise)</p>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>217</td>
<td align=center valign=top>9-Feb-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Te Anau, New Zealand</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Hiked Ben Lomond, went to Te Anau.</p>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>218</td>
<td align=center valign=top>10-Feb-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Te Anau, New Zealand</td>
<td align=center valign=top>G &#038; T on Henry Beach, big BBQ, watched Bridezilla</p>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>219</td>
<td align=center valign=top>11-Feb-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>afloat, Milford Wanderer, New Zealand</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Pissing wet, great cruise, kayak and loads of food</p>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>220</td>
<td align=center valign=top>12-Feb-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Luxmore Hut, Kepler Track, New Zealand</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Nice cruise, Kepler Track day 1<br />
</table>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>&#8220;Ben Lomond is my nemesis&#8221; &#8211; 10th January 2003</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2013/02/13/ben-lomond-is-my-nemesis-10th-january-2003/</link>
				<pubDate>Wed, 13 Feb 2013 05:34:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=1516</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[(Being a re-post of a ten-year old Yahoo groups newsletter update) [Internet Laundromat, Te Anau, New Zealand] &#8220;Ben Lomond is my nemesis&#8221; was what Danika was feeling the day before yesterday as we hiked up the Ben Lomond in Queenstown. This mountain is higher, steeper and more difficult than the Ben Lomond that we hiked &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2013/02/13/ben-lomond-is-my-nemesis-10th-january-2003/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "&#8220;Ben Lomond is my nemesis&#8221; &#8211; 10th January 2003"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><i>(Being a re-post of a ten-year old Yahoo groups newsletter update)</i></p>
<p>[Internet Laundromat, Te Anau, New Zealand]</p>
<p>&#8220;Ben Lomond is my nemesis&#8221; was what Danika was feeling the day before yesterday as we hiked up the Ben Lomond in Queenstown. This mountain is higher, steeper and more difficult than the Ben Lomond that we hiked in Scotland a few months ago. But we made it to the top despite that!</p>
<p>We&#8217;re now in the South Island of New Zealand. Since we emailed last we&#8217;ve hiked the fabulous day walk &#8220;Tongariro Crossing&#8221; (Mordor) which was excellent, driven down to Wellington and taken the ferry across the Cook Strait (accompanied by a few shy dolphins) to the South Island.</p>
<p>We&#8217;ve found that the South Island is bigger and more remote than we expected &#8211; we seem to have spent a lot of time driving about. We&#8217;ve been to the low-key and cute &#8216;cities&#8217; of Christchurch and Dunedin (both far too cold to consider a permanent base) and driven to the picturesque Mt Cook region where we did a little hiking.</p>
<p>After that we headed towards Queenstown, the Adventure and Adrenalin Capital of New Zealand. On the way to Queenstown we stopped off in Alexandra in Central Otago where Gordon went mountain biking. It was good fun (he skipped most of the extreme stuff) and was very similar to East Washington or North California &#8211; strange to be so far away but so similar! After going to Queenstown Danika jumped off a bridge with a little bit of elastic attached to her ankles.</p>
<p>Yup!!! Danika Bungy-jumped from Kawarau Bridge!!! It&#8217;s totally incredible and she still can&#8217;t quite believe she did it &#8211; but if you&#8217;re going to do it, you might as well do it in Queenstown.</p>
<p>Now we&#8217;re down in beautiful Fiordland hanging out in Te Anau. In the next week we&#8217;ve got an overnight trip on Milford Sound and a large 4-day hike in the Kepler mountains to look forward to. Then we start to work away back up New Zealand on the long trek home.</p>
<p>Hope all is well with everyone,</p>
<p>Gordon and Danika</p>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
		<item>
		<title>7th February 2003 &#8211; Queenstown, New Zealand</title>
		<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2013/02/08/7th-february-2003-queenstown-new-zealand/</link>
				<pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2013 05:47:49 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Travel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bluefacedpixie]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=1508</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[And she jumps! While in the Capital of Adventure Danika and I decided we would use some of our travel budget on once-in-a-lifetime experiences. I chose to go helicopter riding later on the South Island (more on this later) and Danika ended up Bungy Jumping in Queenstown. Enough said really. day date overnight activity 213 &#8230; <a href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2013/02/08/7th-february-2003-queenstown-new-zealand/" class="more-link">Continue reading<span class="screen-reader-text"> "7th February 2003 &#8211; Queenstown, New Zealand"</span></a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>And she jumps!</p>
<p>While in the Capital of Adventure Danika and I decided we would use some of our travel budget on once-in-a-lifetime experiences.  I chose to go helicopter riding later on the South Island (more on this later) and Danika ended up Bungy Jumping in Queenstown.  Enough said really.</p>
<table width=100% cellpadding=1 cellspacing=4 border=0>
<tr>
<th align=center valign=top width=35>day</th>
<th align=center valign=top width=100>date</th>
<th align=center valign=top width=35%>overnight</th>
<th align=center valign=top>activity</th>
</tr>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>213</td>
<td align=center valign=top>5-Feb-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Alexandra, New Zealand</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Dunedin Peninsula</p>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>214</td>
<td align=center valign=top>6-Feb-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Queenstown, New Zealand</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Went biking in Alexandra, Arrowtown/Ford of Bruinen, watched bungy</p>
<tr>
<td align=center valign=top>215</td>
<td align=center valign=top>7-Feb-03</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Queenstown, New Zealand</td>
<td align=center valign=top>Danika bungies<br />
</table>
]]></content:encoded>
										</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
