<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	
	>
<channel>
	<title>
	Comments on: Ruminations on camera buying	</title>
	<atom:link href="https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/01/30/ruminations-on-camera-buying/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/01/30/ruminations-on-camera-buying/</link>
	<description>Just another WordPress site</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2006 07:12:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.2.4</generator>
			<item>
				<title>
				By: bfp				</title>
				<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/01/30/ruminations-on-camera-buying/#comment-44</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[bfp]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2006 07:12:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=131#comment-44</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[The Pentax did tempt me - but I think it was the &quot;common man&quot; approach to the Nikon (lots of lenses, articles, fellow users) which swayed me.   The Pentax did not look good on paper but in-hand it was a nice fit, although its menu system seemed a little strange and the demo pictures lacked life.   In terms of menus I still find Konica-Minolta the best, although it looks like the D50 will be straightforward and as confusing as any Digital camera (far less SLR) can be.]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The Pentax did tempt me &#8211; but I think it was the &#8220;common man&#8221; approach to the Nikon (lots of lenses, articles, fellow users) which swayed me.   The Pentax did not look good on paper but in-hand it was a nice fit, although its menu system seemed a little strange and the demo pictures lacked life.   In terms of menus I still find Konica-Minolta the best, although it looks like the D50 will be straightforward and as confusing as any Digital camera (far less SLR) can be.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
						<item>
				<title>
				By: MartinG				</title>
				<link>https://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/2006/01/30/ruminations-on-camera-buying/#comment-43</link>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[MartinG]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2006 08:50:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://machaggis.net/bluefacedpixie/?p=131#comment-43</guid>
					<description><![CDATA[Hey, haven&#039;t posted here in a wee while ... Yah, from my limited non-geek knowledge the DSLRs look very excellent value now - I like the D50, but I have a soft spot for Pentax cameras too; my chemical SLR is a Pentax, and results of my snapping have always satisfied. 

Cool camera though, that Nikon :) I wouldn&#039;t say no.]]></description>
		<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hey, haven&#8217;t posted here in a wee while &#8230; Yah, from my limited non-geek knowledge the DSLRs look very excellent value now &#8211; I like the D50, but I have a soft spot for Pentax cameras too; my chemical SLR is a Pentax, and results of my snapping have always satisfied. </p>
<p>Cool camera though, that Nikon 🙂 I wouldn&#8217;t say no.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
						</item>
			</channel>
</rss>
